{
  "_comment": "BROWSERFIREFOXHIDE data/trivia_questions.json",
  "genericWrongAnswers": {
    "names": [
      "Beru Lars", "Arturito", "Ello Asty", "Carrie Fisher", "Dak Ralter", "Danz Borin", "Matthew Wood", "James Earl Jones", "Richard Marquand", "Chief Chirpa", "Christopher Lee", "Daniel Craig", "J.J. Abrams's assistant Morgan Dameron", "Andy Serkis", "Peter Cushing", "Billy Dee Williams", "Harrison Ford", "J.J. Abrams", "Billie Lourd", "Shelby Young", "Rachel Butera", "Carolyn Hennesy", "Nien Nunb", "Darth Tyranus", "Yuzzum", "Rian Johnson", "Jon Favreau", "Ki-Adi-Mundi", "TK-421", "Fode And Beed", "Rugor Nass", "Peter Serafinowicz", "Ozzeo", "Captain Needa", "Younglings", "Embo", "Maz Katana", "Gardulla Besadii the Elder", "Rose Tico", "Zam Wesell", "Paige Tico", "Captain Panaka", "Taun We", "Boga", "Wicket", "Lor San Tekka", "Tallissan Lintra", "Temiri Blagg", "Porkins", "Watt Tambor", "Adi Gallia", "Admiral Motti", "Admiral Piett", "Admiral Raddus", "Allegiant General Pryde", "Aayla Secura", "Bala-Tik", "Baze Malbus", "Beru Lars (Whitesun)", "Boss Nass", "Commander D'Acy", "DJ", "Dr. Cornelius Evazan", "Enfys Nest", "Red Leader", "General Cassio Tagge", "General Crix Madine", "General Draven", "General Rieekan", "General Veers", "Jannah", "Jocasta Nu", "Gold Leader", "Kanan Jarrus", "Lady Proxima", "Lama Su", "Lieutenant Mitaka", "Luminara Unduli", "Lyra Erso", "Moff Jerjerrod", "Plo Koon", "Poggle the Lesser", "Ponda Baba", "Queen Apailana", "Ric Olie", "Rio Durant", "Rune Haako", "Sio Bibble", "Tion Medon", "Unkar Plutt", "Val", "Wicket W. Warrick", "Director Krennic", "Dryden Vos", "Galen Erso", "Grand Moff Tarkin", "Jyn Erso", "K-2SO", "L3-37", "Mon Mothma", "Qi'ra", "Saw Gerrera", "Tobias Beckett", "Vice Admiral Holdo", "Zorii Bliss", "David Prowse", "Oscar the Grouch and Chewbacca", "Big Bird and Princess Leia", "Elmo and an Ewok", "Ian McKellen", "Sean Connery", "Christopher Reeve", "Shelley Winters", "Barbara Stanwyck", "Ethel Merman", "Omar Sharif", "Jack Hawkins", "Claude Rains", "Prince Xizor", "Suri", "Jabba the Hutt", "Optimus Prime", "T-1000", "Felicity Jones", "Emilia Clarke", "Chris Farley", "Admiral Ackbar", "Zuvio", "Steven Spielberg", "Irvin Kershner", "Bossk", "Snap Wexley", "Strono 'Cookie' Tuggs", "Cal Alder", "Bren Derlin", "BoShek", "Wuher", "Wes Janson", "Cutup", "Aemon Gremm", "Aurodia Ventafoli", "Kodyok", "Ters Ksi"
    ],
    "places": [
      "Mos Eisley Cantina", "Dantooine", "Anoat", "Norway", "The Kessel Run", "Tosche Station", "The Sluis Sector and The Anoat Sector", "D'Qar", "Abafar", "Agamar", "Ajan Kloss", "Akiva", "Alaris Prime", "Aldhani", "Aleen", "Alzoc III", "Anaxes", "Ando", "At Achrann", "At Acoda", "At Aravin", "At Arissa", "At Attin", "At Aytuu", "Atollon", "Barton IV", "Balnab", "Batuu", "Bogano", "Bora Vio", "Bracca", "Brendok", "Cantonica", "Castilon", "Cato Neimoidia", "Chandrila", "Christophsis", "Concord Dawn", "Daiyu", "Devaron", "Eadu", "Endor (planet)", "Erakit", "Eriadu", "Esseles", "Ferrix", "Florrum", "Fondor", "Ghorman", "Hosnian Prime", "Iego", "Iridonia", "Jabiim", "Jelucan", "Jestefad", "Kef Bir", "Khofar", "Koboh", "Kuat", "Lah'mu", "Lothal", "Lotho Minor", "Malachor", "Malastare", "Manaan", "Mapuzo", "Maridun", "Mimban", "Mina-Rau", "Mon Cala", "Mortis", "Nal Hutta", "Narkina 5", "Nevarro", "Niamos", "Numidian Prime", "Nur", "Oba Diah", "Observatory Moon", "Olega", "Onderon", "Ord Mantell", "Ossus", "Pabu", "Pasaana", "Peridea", "Pillio", "Raada", "Rishi", "Rodia", "Rugosa", "Ruusan", "Ryloth", "Saleucami", "Savareen", "Seatos", "Serenno", "Shili", "Sissubo", "Skako Minor", "Sorgan", "Subterrel", "Sullust", "Tanalorr", "Taris", "Telos", "Teth", "Toydaria", "Trandosha", "Ueda", "Umbara", "Vandor", "Vardos", "Wayland", "Wobani", "Wrea", "Yavin", "Zeffo", "Zygerria", "Tatooine", "Bay 4", "Bay 2187", "Bay 1138", "Coruscant", "Naboo", "Venezuela", "Brazil", "Mountain Top", "Low base level", "Inner Rim", "Unknown Regions", "Mid Rim", "Isle of Skye", "Porg Island", "Gardner Pinnacles"
    ],
    "numbers": [
      "Seven", "Four (Episodes I - IV)", "Approximately 2,002,795,192", "IV", "About one year", "Over 6 million", "Twenty", "More than 20,000", "120 kilometers", "Three", "Five", "II", "VI", "66", "I", "VIII", "III", "V", "VII", "3263827", "1,000", "Two meters", "7'6\"", "67", "Two", "Six", "Eight", "Ten", "Eleven", "Thirteen", "Fifteen", "Seventeen", "Eighteen", "Twenty-one", "Twenty-three", "Twenty-four", "Twenty-five", "Twenty-six", "Twenty-seven", "Twenty-eight", "Twenty-nine", "Thirty", "1975", "1979", "1981", "One hundred", "Over ten thousand", "At least five hundred", "3", "5", "4", "2-3 seasons", "6-7 seasons", "9-12 seasons", "0.4", "0.6", "0.1", "10", "12", "2.3 meters", "1.4 meters", "2.0 meters", "3.1 meters"
    ],
    "quotes": [
      "'Obi Wan killed your father'", "\"I have a bad feeling about this\"", "\"Obi-Wan...there...is good in him. I know there is\"", "\"May the Force be with you\"", "\"Would it help if I got out and pushed?\"", "\"There's always a bigger fish\"", "\"The ability to speak does not make you intelligent\"", "\"Ya-hoo!\"", "\"No, I am your father\"", "'If only you knew the power of the dark side.'", "'Size matters not. Look at me. Judge me by my size, do you?'", "'The Force is not a power you have. It's not about lifting rocks.'", "'An object cannot make you good or evil. The temptation of power, forbidden knowledge, even the desire to do good can lead some down that path.'", "'I'm one with the Force. The Force is with me.'", "'This holiday is yours, where we all share with you the hope that this day brings us closer to freedom and to harmony and to peace.'", "You're exactly the way I remember you in my dreams.", "'I see through the lies of the Jedi. I do not fear the dark side as you do.'", "'His deeds will not be forgiven until he merits'", "You were right,", "What happened to 'then?'", "Are we being too literal, sir?", "We ain't found sh*t.", "It's Mega Maid, sir! She's gone from suck to blow!", "I always have coffee when I watch radar, you know that!", "What's the matter Colonel Sanderz? Chicken?", "If you can read this, you don't need glasses.", "I can't breathe in this thing.", "You idiots! These are not them! You've captured their stunt doubles!", "The ship is too big. If I walk, the movie will be over.", "Now you see that evil will always triumph because good is dumb.", "Listen, we're not just doing this for money. We're doing it for a s***load of money!", "God willing, we'll all meet again in Spaceballs 2: The search for more money.", "Look, your highness, it's not that we're afraid. Far from it.", "Please, please, don't make a fuss. I'm just plain yogurt.", "I'm a mawg: half man, half dog. I'm my own best friend.", "May the Schwartz be with you.", "You listen! On this ship, you're to refer to me as 'idiot,' not 'you captain.'", "So the combination is 1, 2, 3, 4, 5? That's the stupidest combination I ever heard in my life!", "Oh, no! Not again!", "Will they live?", "Will they survive?", "Will it come true?", "Forgotten", "Cherished", "Memorialized", "'I love you, too'", "Too late", "Thank you", "Our only hope", "The only hope", "The rebel's only hope", "'Impressive. Every word in that sentence was ___'", "Nonsense", "Correct", "Misleading", "'___. It's a space station.'", "It's not a moon", "That's not a moon", "Is that a moon?", "'When I left you, I was but the learner, now I am the ___'", "Jedi", "Friend", "Teacher"
    ],
    "other": [
      "An exhaust tube", "Star Wars: The Empire Strikes Back, released on the Atari 2600", "Life Day", "Jingle All the Way (1996)", "High Jedi General", "Revenge of the Jedi", "Yellow", "Kyber crystal", "A monkey", "The Jawa Sandcrawler", "Star Wars Holiday Special", "NSYNC", "Buffy", "Disney+", "Blue and white", "True!", "An Alaskan Malamute", "A chimpanzee", "Stardust", "Yaddle", "T-16 skyhopper", "A New Hope", "An AT-AT", "He lost his right arm", "An honor debt", "He was a navigator on a spice freighter", "Red", "Sanitation", "He used an ancient Jedi mind trick on Bib Fortuna", "Yoda's species is unknown", "His faith in his friends", "Wookiee", "A god", "C-3PO was naked", "For more than 1,000 generations", "DC-15A", "BB-8", "A DL-44 pistol", "Confront Darth Vader again", "He didn't agree with it", "Charming", "\"No, there is another\"", "Shyriiwook", "It gives him focus and makes him stronger", "Because of his father", "A Separatist", "Their life", "To find a Padawan that deserved his training", "He dreamed that Padme died in childbirth", "Hutt", "Little freaks", "They were worried", "In the left shoulder", "He hated it", "2187", "Snow and ice", "Jabba Desilijic Tiure", "Kitik Keed'kak", "Captain", "He was disintegrated", "Gungan", "Padme Naberrie", "\"Captain\"", "Shmi Skywalker", "An angel", "He was too clumsy", "Toydarian", "Puffins", "Starkiller", "An Astromech", "She has lost the will to live", "He's thrown into a pit for Chewbacca to eat him", "Rebel bombers", "Supreme Leader Snoke connected them", "Green", "Dianoga", "Slave I", "Ilum Crystals", "Han Solo and Princess Leia", "Itchy", "They're in tune with the Force and know how to work with it", "Chaos Walking", "Alderaan, Princess Leia's home planet", "Jawas, Ewoks", "Zabraks", "Gungans", "Rodians", "Zeltrons", "Bothans", "Keshiri", "Falleen", "Chiss", "Hutts", "Rakata", "and so on", "An icy world and a source for crystals used in lightsabers", "The capital planet of the Corellian system populated by pirates and shipbuilders", "Han", "Yes, it's true", "Yes", "Jedi", "Emerald green", "Moisture farmers", "The ship got named after a bird of prey, the Bat Falcon", "Adventures of Luke Starkiller, As Taken From the Journal of the Whills, Saga 1: The Star Wars", "Rey and Kylo first come across one another when Kylo captures her on the planet Takodana", "Probot", "The Last Jedi", "Organa", "Tusken Raiders", "Rancor", "Jawa", "Ion cannons", "TaunTaun", "The Darksaber", "Togruta", "The Beastie Boys", "Wampas", "Jabba the Hutt", "Elephant", "The Great Purge", "Star Wars: The Rise of Skywalker", "Galactic Basic", "Blast Shield", "The Empire Strikes Back", "The Millennium Falcon", "Her handmaiden Sabe", "Way", "Two (Rule of Two)", "True", "Hope", "A beskar spear", "A Sithway finder", "A spice runner", "Boba Fett's armor", "The Sith", "A First Order Captain's medallion", "A dyad in the Force", "The First Order", "Burns It", "The Jawas", "Hyperdrive", "All Terrain Armored Transport", "The Boonta Eve Classic", "November 17th", "Ancient Hebrew", "Twin Ion Engines", "Mon Calamari", "Hibernation sickness", "Salt", "Death Troopers", "Midi-chlorions", "He didn't have one", "The Battle of Endor", "The death of the last two Sith Lords", "Samurai", "The Galactic Civil War", "He was a smuggler", "Solo rescued him from enslavement by the Empire", "The Cave of Evil", "The Separatists. Confederacy of Independent Systems (CIS) is also acceptable", "Four; two green and two blue", "Han and Leia", "Kylo's fall to the Dark Side and massacre of Luke's other students", "Yoda (as a Force ghost)", "An astromech droid", "The Sarlaac Pit", "In the cave on Dagobah, where he briefly battled a spectral Vader", "BB-8 informs her he's wearing Poe Dameron's jacket", "Rathtars", "A standard First Order TIE Fighter", "A Dreadnaught", "A bongo", "Jawa Juice", "A nexu", "His mechanical right arm", "Red Two", "Bith", "A Krayt Dragon", "\"Jedi Rocks\"", "The Y-Wing", "Slip", "Nantoon", "Silencer", "Thala-siren", "Don't Join", "The Praetorian Guards", "Porgs", "Ugnaughts", "A Bacta Tank", "Corellian YT-1300f", "Tibanna gas", "Adi Gallia", "Admiral Motti", "Admiral Piett", "Admiral Raddus", "Allegiant General Pryde", "Aayla Secura", "Bala-Tik", "Baze Malbus", "Beru Lars (Whitesun)", "Boss Nass", "Commander D'Acy", "DJ", "Dr. Cornelius Evazan", "Enfys Nest", "Red Leader", "General Cassio Tagge", "General Crix Madine", "General Draven", "General Rieekan", "General Veers", "Abafar", "Agamar", "Ajan Kloss", "Akiva", "Alaris Prime", "Aldhani", "Aleen", "Alzoc III", "Anaxes", "Ando", "At Achrann", "At Acoda", "At Aravin", "At Arissa", "At Attin", "At Aytuu", "Atollon", "Barton IV", "Balnab", "Batuu", "Red 7", "Dark", "Villain", "Force", "Blue", "Ghost", "Apparition", "Spirit", "The Power Within", "The Marshmallow", "They also use the Force", "white", "black", "Chancellor", "President", "King", "Ebon Hawk", "Outrider", "George Lucas bought it back", "Industrial Light and Magic, LLC", "Mattel, Inc.", "Side Trip", "Interlude at Darkknell", "X-wing: Rogue Squadron", "Missed Chance", "The Arbitrator", "Eclipse", "Quarren", "A dragonsnake", "A rock", "Cheat", "Jerk", "His datapad", "His ID card", "Violence", "War", "Bad servomotor", "Bad communicator", "Bad wheels", "Smoke", "Light", "Moisture", "Foul-smelling", "Shabby-looking", "Rotten-smelling", "Coruscant-class freighter", "Baleen-class bulk freighter", "Coruscant YT bulk freighter", "A tuneup", "A polish", "A restart", "FX-12", "FY-9", "2-2B", "Age 6", "Age 3", "Age 10", "Scrawny", "Lackey", "Catapults", "Rocks", "Ropes", "A wampa", "A tauntaun", "An Ewok", "Thoughts", "Ears", "Memories", "Jedi", "Girl", "Water", "Coaxium", "9", "4", "6", "Finn", "Carbon-freezing chamber", "Oil bath", "Surgical pod", "3", "1", "IG-88", "Green", "Biggs Darklighter", "Wedge Antilles", "Admiral Ozzel", "Captain Needa", "Bulk freighter", "Cargo ship", "TIE fighter", "Lieutenant", "Pilot", "Turbo Infused Engine", "Trans Ion Engine", "Twin Infused Engine", "A negative ionizer", "A coupling", "A magnetic grapple", "Moriz", "Maurice", "Lance", "Neimoidian", "Duros", "A blue milk", "A meiloorun fruit", "Secret handshake", "To the repair shop", "To the hanger bay", "On a walk", "The truth", "Justice", "Sleep mode", "Hibernation mode", "Power off mode", "Plasma cannon", "Cloaking devices", "Laser cannon", "Webbing", "Restraining bolt", "Rockets", "Wuher", "893 to 1", "1,298 to 1", "1,138 to 1", "His helmet", "His blaster", "His droid", "Best friend", "Astromech", "Co-pilot", "Takodana", "Allegiance", "Chimaera", "TIE bomber", "Hydro", "Hosnian", "He couldn't talk", "He couldn't breathe", "He threw up", "Antigravity chamber", "Emergency air dump", "Laser tunnel", "Admiral", "General", "1", "0", "A Jawa", "A Twi'lek", "A Kowakian Monkey-Lizard", "Meilooruns", "T-7 Ion Disruptors", "Transponders", "Cad Bane", "A murder", "A mob", "A flock", "A cluster", "Rootleaf Stew", "Space waffles", "Colo Claw Fish", "Deep-Fried Nuna Legs", "Cool", "Rigid", "Imperial", "Logray", "A Cave", "The Millennium Falcon", "A Scrap Heap", "What are you doing here?", "How did you find me?", "Where's Han?", "9", "7", "Q-Tips", "Matches", "Clothespins", "Colo Claw Fish", "Opee Sea Killer", "Anacondan", "50,000", "40,000", "10,000", "Bobbajo", "Trash", "Junk", "Meanies", "Five", "Six", "Blaster Bolts", "Electricity", "A Tiny Net", "Battle droids", "Keeradaks", "The dark", "A Marshal Commander", "A Clone Sergeant", "A Special Ops trooper", "CT-1429", "CT-4040", "CT-1405", "Yalbec Prime", "Geonosis", "Pantora", "A landspeeder", "Another TIE fighter", "Beggar's Canyon", "Hyperdrive", "Escape Pod", "Coolant Control", "13", "24", "21", "A door opening", "Hum of a lightsaber", "Music", "Ignores him", "Embraces him", "High Five", "Training as a Jedi", "The light side", "Being a Jedi", "6", "Rust Bucket", "Metal Menace", "Rolling Junk Pile", "Soka", "Shorty", "Stardust", "1.74 meters", "0.81 meters", "2.20 meters", "Eight", "Aurra Sing", "Sy Snootles", "Mama the Hutt", "Yamak", "Wampa", "Mynock", "Kamino"
    ]
  },
  "loadingItems": [
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "What is Luke Skywalker's home planet?", "correctAnswer": "Tatooine", "cleverWrong": "Jakku" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What color is Mace Windu's lightsaber?", "correctAnswer": "Purple", "cleverWrong": "Yellow" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "In The Rise of Skywalker, Rey is revealed to be the granddaughter of which Star Wars character?", "correctAnswer": "Palpatine", "cleverWrong": "Obi-Wan Kenobi" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "What message does Princess Leia send to Obi-Wan Kenobi in A New Hope?", "correctAnswer": "Help me, Obi-Wan Kenobi - you're my only hope", "cleverWrong": "These are not the droids you're looking for" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who built C-3PO?", "correctAnswer": "Anakin Skywalker", "cleverWrong": "The Jawas" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "On which planet did Anakin Skywalker and Padme Amidala first meet?", "correctAnswer": "Tatooine", "cleverWrong": "Naboo" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "Around how old is Yoda when he trains Luke Skywalker in The Empire Strikes Back?", "correctAnswer": "900 years old", "cleverWrong": "800 years old" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which characters escape Jakku aboard the Millennium Falcon in The Force Awakens?", "correctAnswer": "Rey, Finn and BB-8", "cleverWrong": "Rey, Poe and BB-8" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What species is Chewbacca?", "correctAnswer": "Wookiee", "cleverWrong": "Ewok" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who plays Obi-Wan Kenobi in the original Star Wars trilogy?", "correctAnswer": "Alec Guinness", "cleverWrong": "Ewan McGregor" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "What does Han Solo say after Princess Leia tells him she loves him in The Empire Strikes Back?", "correctAnswer": "I know", "cleverWrong": "I love you too" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How old was Padme Amidala when she was elected Queen of Naboo?", "correctAnswer": "14", "cleverWrong": "16" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What was Finn's stormtrooper code name in The Force Awakens?", "correctAnswer": "FN-2187", "cleverWrong": "TK-421" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What bear-like species inhabit the forest moon of Endor in Return of the Jedi?", "correctAnswer": "Ewoks", "cleverWrong": "Wookies" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who plays Anakin Skywalker in the Star Wars prequels?", "correctAnswer": "Hayden Christensen", "cleverWrong": "Jake Lloyd" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who strikes down Obi-Wan Kenobi in A New Hope?", "correctAnswer": "Darth Vader", "cleverWrong": "A stormtrooper" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What was Yoda's home planet?", "correctAnswer": "He never reveals his home planet", "cleverWrong": "Dagobah" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What species is Jar Jar Binks?", "correctAnswer": "Gungan", "cleverWrong": "Nautolan" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Who adopts Luke Skywalker after he's born?", "correctAnswer": "His step-uncle", "cleverWrong": "Bail Organa" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who gave Kylo Ren the scar on his face?", "correctAnswer": "Rey", "cleverWrong": "Finn" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What is the name of the bounty hunter who captures Han Solo in The Empire Strikes Back?", "correctAnswer": "Boba Fett", "cleverWrong": "IG-88" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What species is Darth Maul?", "correctAnswer": "Dathomirian", "cleverWrong": "Sith" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Who typically wields a blue lightsaber?", "correctAnswer": "A Jedi Guardian", "cleverWrong": "A Jedi Consular" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What body part does Luke Skywalker lose during his fight with Darth Vader in The Empire Strikes Back?", "correctAnswer": "His right hand", "cleverWrong": "His foot" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who issued Order 66 in Revenge of the Sith?", "correctAnswer": "Palpatine", "cleverWrong": "Commander Cody" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Where does Rey find Luke Skywalker at the end of The Force Awakens?", "correctAnswer": "Ahch-To", "cleverWrong": "Dagobah" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What vehicle does a young Anakin Skywalker race in The Phantom Menace?", "correctAnswer": "Podracer", "cleverWrong": "Swoop bike" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which two comedians voice BB-8?", "correctAnswer": "Bill Hader and Ben Schwartz", "cleverWrong": "Seth Rogen and Bill Burr" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "How is Kylo Ren related to Luke Skywalker?", "correctAnswer": "Kylo Ren is Luke Skywalker's nephew", "cleverWrong": "Kylo Ren is Luke Skywalker's son" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who killed Jabba the Hutt in Return of the Jedi?", "correctAnswer": "Princess Leia", "cleverWrong": "Luke Skywalker" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "In Star Wars, what is the energy created by all life that connects everything in the universe?", "correctAnswer": "The Force", "cleverWrong": "Midi-chlorians" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is Poe Dameron's job in the Resistance's Starfighter Corps?", "correctAnswer": "Fighter pilot", "cleverWrong": "General" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who witnessed Padme Amidala and Anakin Skywalker's marriage?", "correctAnswer": "R2-D2 and C-3PO", "cleverWrong": "Obi-Wan Kenobi" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What is Kylo Ren's real name?", "correctAnswer": "Ben Solo", "cleverWrong": "Ben Skywalker" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What was the name of the space station commonly considered the Empire's deadliest weapon?", "correctAnswer": "The Death Star", "cleverWrong": "Starkiller Base" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many languages can C-3PO speak?", "correctAnswer": "Over 6 million", "cleverWrong": "Over 1 million" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "On which planet do Anakin Skywalker and Obi-Wan Kenobi duel in Revenge of the Sith?", "correctAnswer": "Mustafar", "cleverWrong": "Geonosis" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "What does Luke Skywalker say when Darth Vader tells him he's his father in The Empire Strikes Back?", "correctAnswer": "No - no - that's not true - that's impossible", "cleverWrong": "No! That's a lie!" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who plays Padme Amidala in the Star Wars prequels?", "correctAnswer": "Natalie Portman", "cleverWrong": "Keira Knightley" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who owned the Millennium Falcon before Han Solo?", "correctAnswer": "Lando Calrissian", "cleverWrong": "Chewbacca" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who said 'I'm just a simple man trying to make my way in the universe'?", "correctAnswer": "Jango Fett", "cleverWrong": "Boba Fett" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "What's the name of the bar first seen in A New Hope?", "correctAnswer": "Mos Eisley Cantina", "cleverWrong": "Dex's Diner" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which high-ranking official in the First Order was revealed to be a spy for the Resistance in The Rise of Skywalker?", "correctAnswer": "General Hux", "cleverWrong": "Captain Phasma" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How old was Anakin Skywalker when he fought in the Clone Wars?", "correctAnswer": "19", "cleverWrong": "22" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "What is Chewbacca's home planet?", "correctAnswer": "Kashyyyk", "cleverWrong": "Endor" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who kills Han Solo in The Force Awakens?", "correctAnswer": "Kylo Ren", "cleverWrong": "Supreme Leader Snoke" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "What are Yoda's dying words in Return of the Jedi?", "correctAnswer": "There is another Skywalker", "cleverWrong": "The Force will be with you. Always" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which character has appeared in the most Star Wars films?", "correctAnswer": "C-3PO", "cleverWrong": "R2-D2" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who said 'The dark side of the Force is a pathway to many abilities some consider to be unnatural'?", "correctAnswer": "Palpatine", "cleverWrong": "Count Dooku" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "What year was Episode I - The Phantom Menace released?", "correctAnswer": "1999", "cleverWrong": "1997" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What kind of lightsaber did Darth Maul originally have in The Phantom Menace?", "correctAnswer": "A double-bladed lightsaber", "cleverWrong": "Two separate lightsabers" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is the highest-grossing Star Wars movie?", "correctAnswer": "The Force Awakens", "cleverWrong": "A New Hope" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many Jedi sit on the Jedi Council?", "correctAnswer": "12", "cleverWrong": "9" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Where did George Lucas film scenes of the planet Tatooine in A New Hope?", "correctAnswer": "Death Valley National Park", "cleverWrong": "Sahara Desert" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which character from the original Star Wars trilogy is given a message at the end of Rogue One?", "correctAnswer": "Princess Leia", "cleverWrong": "Luke Skywalker" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who shares a kiss with Rey at the end of The Rise of Skywalker?", "correctAnswer": "Ben Solo", "cleverWrong": "Finn" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Where were Luke Skywalker and Princess Leia born?", "correctAnswer": "Polis Massa", "cleverWrong": "Naboo" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What is the name of Anakin Skywalker's mother?", "correctAnswer": "Shmi", "cleverWrong": "Beru" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What material is Han Solo frozen in during The Empire Strikes Back?", "correctAnswer": "Carbonite", "cleverWrong": "Beskar" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who does BB-8 belong to?", "correctAnswer": "Poe Dameron", "cleverWrong": "Rey" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Which planet is 'Cloud City' located on?", "correctAnswer": "Bespin", "cleverWrong": "Coruscant" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is the highest rank a Jedi can achieve in the Jedi Order?", "correctAnswer": "Grand Master", "cleverWrong": "Jedi Master" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How much money did A New Hope make at the box office?", "correctAnswer": "$775.8 million", "cleverWrong": "$530.2 million" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "What famous words appear in every Star Wars opening crawl?", "correctAnswer": "A long time ago in a galaxy far, far away --", "cleverWrong": "May the Force be with you" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who kills Qui-Gon Jinn in The Phantom Menace?", "correctAnswer": "Darth Maul", "cleverWrong": "Darth Sidious" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who gave Luke Skywalker's lightsaber to Finn in The Force Awakens?", "correctAnswer": "Maz Kanata", "cleverWrong": "Han Solo" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What does Yoda say is the path to the dark side?", "correctAnswer": "Fear", "cleverWrong": "Anger" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Where was the base for the Rebel Alliance located in A New Hope?", "correctAnswer": "Yavin 4", "cleverWrong": "Hoth" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who plays Luke Skywalker?", "correctAnswer": "Mark Hamill", "cleverWrong": "Harrison Ford" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "How did Finn become a stormtrooper?", "correctAnswer": "He was sold to the First Order as a child", "cleverWrong": "He enlisted voluntarily" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "What day is commonly known as 'Star Wars Day'?", "correctAnswer": "May 4th", "cleverWrong": "May 25th" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is the name of the holographic board game played aboard the Millennium Falcon?", "correctAnswer": "Dejarik", "cleverWrong": "Holochess" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is the connection between Kylo Ren and Ben Solo?", "correctAnswer": "Kylo Ren is Ben Solo's alter ego", "cleverWrong": "They are brothers" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Why can't Jedi get married?", "correctAnswer": "Attachment and possession are forbidden in the Jedi Order", "cleverWrong": "They take a vow of celibacy" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "At the end of Return of the Jedi, Darth Vader returns to the Light Side and becomes Anakin Skywalker again. What are his final words to Luke?", "correctAnswer": "Tell your sister you were right", "cleverWrong": "Now, go, my son. Leave me" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who plays The Mandalorian in the TV show The Mandalorian?", "correctAnswer": "Pedro Pascal", "cleverWrong": "Jon Favreau" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who saves Darth Vader from the lava banks of Mustafar at the end of Revenge of the Sith?", "correctAnswer": "Palpatine", "cleverWrong": "Obi-Wan Kenobi" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What is the name of Jyn's father in Rogue One?", "correctAnswer": "Galen Erso", "cleverWrong": "Krennic" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What is Baby Yoda's real name?", "correctAnswer": "Grogu", "cleverWrong": "Yaddle" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who adopted Princess Leia?", "correctAnswer": "Bail and Breha Organa", "cleverWrong": "Owen and Beru Lars" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "What is Han Solo's home planet?", "correctAnswer": "Corellia", "cleverWrong": "Kashyyyk" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "What year was Return of the Jedi released?", "correctAnswer": "1983", "cleverWrong": "1980" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Which movie comes first chronologically in the Star Wars universe: Rogue One or Solo: A Star Wars Story?", "correctAnswer": "Solo: A Star Wars Story", "cleverWrong": "Rogue One" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "On which planet did Yoda train Luke in The Empire Strikes Back?", "correctAnswer": "Dagobah", "cleverWrong": "Yavin 4" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who rules the First Order?", "correctAnswer": "Supreme Leader Snoke", "cleverWrong": "Kylo Ren" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who created Star Wars?", "correctAnswer": "George Lucas", "cleverWrong": "Steven Spielberg" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Kurt Russell was considered for, and eventually turned down, which role in the first Star Wars movie?", "correctAnswer": "Luke Skywalker", "cleverWrong": "Han Solo" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What was Cassian Andor's job in the Rebel Alliance in Rogue One?", "correctAnswer": "Intelligence officer", "cleverWrong": "Fighter pilot" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which Disney character is Jar Jar Binks based on?", "correctAnswer": "Goofy", "cleverWrong": "Donald Duck" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What important information does R2-D2 carry with him in the beginning of Star Wars: A New Hope?", "correctAnswer": "Plans for the Death Star", "cleverWrong": "A message from Yoda" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What was Obi-Wan Kenobi's relationship to Anakin Skywalker?", "correctAnswer": "Obi-Wan was Anakin's master", "cleverWrong": "Obi-Wan was Anakin's father" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What did the Death Star resemble?", "correctAnswer": "A moon", "cleverWrong": "A planet" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "True or false: Al Pacino turned down the role of Han Solo.", "correctAnswer": "True", "cleverWrong": "False" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who plays Lando Calrissian in Solo: A Star Wars Story?", "correctAnswer": "Donald Glover", "cleverWrong": "Billy Dee Williams" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is Boba Fett's ship called?", "correctAnswer": "Slave I", "cleverWrong": "The Razor Crest" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who plays Obi-Wan Kenobi in the Star Wars prequels?", "correctAnswer": "Ewan McGregor", "cleverWrong": "Alec Guinness" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "What episode number is A New Hope?", "correctAnswer": "IV", "cleverWrong": "I" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What type of planet is Tatooine?", "correctAnswer": "A desert planet", "cleverWrong": "A forest planet" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Which planet does the Death Star destroy in A New Hope?", "correctAnswer": "Alderaan", "cleverWrong": "Yavin 4" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who voices Yoda in the Star Wars movies?", "correctAnswer": "Frank Oz", "cleverWrong": "Jim Henson" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What did Luke Skywalker use to distract Darth Vader during their duel in Empire Strikes Back?", "correctAnswer": "An exhaust tube", "cleverWrong": "A loose cable" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What was the original title of Return of the Jedi, used in a teaser trailer in 1982?", "correctAnswer": "Revenge of the Jedi", "cleverWrong": "Shadow of the Empire" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "When Rey pulls out and activates her own lightsaber for the first time at the end of Star Wars: The Rise of Skywalker, what color is it?", "correctAnswer": "Yellow", "cleverWrong": "White" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What type of dog was the inspiration for Chewbacca according to George Lucas?", "correctAnswer": "An Alaskan Malamute", "cleverWrong": "A Shih Tzu" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who was Boba Fett's father?", "correctAnswer": "Jango Fett", "cleverWrong": "Mandalore the Great" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What was Galen Erso's nickname for his daughter?", "correctAnswer": "Stardust", "cleverWrong": "Little Star" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What model of aircraft did Luke use to \"bullseye Womp Rats\"?", "correctAnswer": "T-16 skyhopper", "cleverWrong": "X-34 landspeeder" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "Han Solo boasted that the Millennium Falcon made the Kessel Run in less than how many parsecs?", "correctAnswer": "12 parsecs", "cleverWrong": "14 parsecs" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What species is Greedo?", "correctAnswer": "Rodian", "cleverWrong": "Duros" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What species is native to Endor?", "correctAnswer": "Ewok", "cleverWrong": "Wookiee" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "According to Master Yoda, how many Sith are always out there?", "correctAnswer": "Two", "cleverWrong": "One" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who played the part of Commander Cody?", "correctAnswer": "Temuera Morrison", "cleverWrong": "Dee Bradley Baker" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who wiped out all of the information about Kamino from the Jedi Temple archives?", "correctAnswer": "Count Dooku", "cleverWrong": "Darth Sidious" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who killed Jabba?", "correctAnswer": "Princess Leia", "cleverWrong": "Luke Skywalker" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who adopted Padme Amidala's daughter?", "correctAnswer": "Bail Organa", "cleverWrong": "Owen Lars" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What name does Obi-Wan Kenobi go by on Tatooine?", "correctAnswer": "Ben", "cleverWrong": "Old Ben" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who first and most famously played the part of Chewbacca?", "correctAnswer": "Peter Mayhew", "cleverWrong": "David Prowse" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who killed Jango Fett?", "correctAnswer": "Mace Windu", "cleverWrong": "Obi-Wan Kenobi" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "According to the Emperor, what was Luke's weakness?", "correctAnswer": "His faith in his friends", "cleverWrong": "His attachment to his father" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many lightsabers does General Grievous wield in his fight with Obi-Wan on Utapau?", "correctAnswer": "Four", "cleverWrong": "Two" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "What did Darth Vader say to Luke about the name \"Anakin Skywalker\"?", "correctAnswer": "That it no longer held any meaning for him", "cleverWrong": "That he destroyed him" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "What was the diameter of the first Death Star?", "correctAnswer": "120 kilometers", "cleverWrong": "160 kilometers" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "According to Yoda, what did Luke need to do in order to complete his training and become a Jedi Master?", "correctAnswer": "Confront Darth Vader again", "cleverWrong": "Build a new lightsaber" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What is Queen Amidala's given name?", "correctAnswer": "Padme Naberrie", "cleverWrong": "Sabe" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What kind of species is Watto?", "correctAnswer": "Toydarian", "cleverWrong": "Hutt" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What was Luke's last name originally going to be?", "correctAnswer": "Starkiller", "cleverWrong": "Skyrunner" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "R2-D2 is classified as what type of droid?", "correctAnswer": "An Astromech", "cleverWrong": "A Protocol Droid" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What color is Yoda's lightsaber?", "correctAnswer": "Green", "cleverWrong": "Blue" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What's the creature which lives in the garbage compactor of the original Death Star called?", "correctAnswer": "Dianoga", "cleverWrong": "Rancor" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What's the substance that powers the lightsabers called?", "correctAnswer": "Ilum Crystals", "cleverWrong": "Kyber Crystals" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What's the Death Star's original commander called?", "correctAnswer": "Grand Moff Tarkin", "cleverWrong": "Admiral Piett" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What's Chewbacca's dad's name?", "correctAnswer": "Itchy", "cleverWrong": "Lumpy" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Both Luke Skywalker and Princess Leia are said to be Force-sensitive. What does that mean?", "correctAnswer": "They're in tune with the Force and know how to work with it", "cleverWrong": "They have a high midi-chlorian count" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What general commanded the military of the Yavin 4 Rebel base?", "correctAnswer": "General Jan Dodonna", "cleverWrong": "Admiral Ackbar" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which character says the following lines? 'An object cannot make you good or evil. The temptation of power, forbidden knowledge, even the desire to do good can lead some down that path.'", "correctAnswer": "Bendu", "cleverWrong": "Ahsoka Tano" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which character says the following lines? 'I'm one with the Force. The Force is with me.'", "correctAnswer": "Chirrut Imwe", "cleverWrong": "Luke Skywalker" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "What odds does C-3P0 provide Han with for successfully navigating the asteroid field?", "correctAnswer": "3,720 to 1", "cleverWrong": "725 to 1" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "What planet is Lando Calrissian from?", "correctAnswer": "Socorro", "cleverWrong": "Bespin" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What's Ilum?", "correctAnswer": "An icy world and a source for crystals used in lightsabers", "cleverWrong": "The home planet of the Sith" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Where does Bail Organa come from?", "correctAnswer": "Alderaan", "cleverWrong": "Coruscant" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What's Corelia?", "correctAnswer": "The capital planet of the Corellian system populated by pirates and shipbuilders", "cleverWrong": "A moon of Endor" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who kissed Princess Leia first?", "correctAnswer": "Luke", "cleverWrong": "Han" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Is it true that Princess Leia killed Jabba the Hut?", "correctAnswer": "Yes, it's true", "cleverWrong": "No, it's false" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Was Princess Leia part of the senate at some point?", "correctAnswer": "Yes", "cleverWrong": "No" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Princess Leia mentors Rey, the last remaining what?", "correctAnswer": "Jedi", "cleverWrong": "Rebel" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What color is Princess Leia's home planet?", "correctAnswer": "Emerald green", "cleverWrong": "Blue and white" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What were Luke's aunt and uncle's jobs on Tatooine?", "correctAnswer": "Moisture farmers", "cleverWrong": "Spice smugglers" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which character is partially named after George Lucas's son?", "correctAnswer": "Dexter Jettster", "cleverWrong": "Kit Fisto" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who is Lando Calrissian's co-pilot in Episode VI: Return of the Jedi?", "correctAnswer": "Nien Nunb", "cleverWrong": "Wedge Antilles" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many engines does the X-Wing Fighter have?", "correctAnswer": "Four", "cleverWrong": "Two" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "The Imperial Probe Droid was also known by another name - which one?", "correctAnswer": "Probot", "cleverWrong": "Seeker Droid" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What is the Sith name of former Jedi Master Count Dooku?", "correctAnswer": "Darth Tyranus", "cleverWrong": "Darth Plagueis" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Clocking in at 2 hours and 32 minutes, which of the 9 movies in the Skywalker Saga is the longest?", "correctAnswer": "The Last Jedi", "cleverWrong": "The Rise of Skywalker" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What is the surname of Princess Leia that is taken from her adoptive parents?", "correctAnswer": "Organa", "cleverWrong": "Amidala" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "On which planet in the Outer Rim Territories do we see Ponda Baba (aka \"Walrus Man\") lose an arm?", "correctAnswer": "Tatooine (in the Mos Eisley Cantina)", "cleverWrong": "Coruscant (in the Outlander Club)" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What outdoorsy people attacked Luke in the Jundland Wastes and helped The Mandalorian beat a krayt dragon?", "correctAnswer": "Tusken Raiders", "cleverWrong": "Jawas" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What 'G' Rodian bounty hunter famously cornered Han Solo in the Mos Eisley Cantina?", "correctAnswer": "Greedo", "cleverWrong": "Bossk" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "What ice planet is the area where the first big battle of \"The Empire Strikes Back\" takes place?", "correctAnswer": "Hoth", "cleverWrong": "Ilum" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What 'R' name applies to the giant creature from Dathomir that Jabba The Hutt keeps in a cave to eat people?", "correctAnswer": "Rancor", "cleverWrong": "Wampa" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "What hyperspace route did Han Solo traverse in the Millennium Falcon in less than 12 parsecs?", "correctAnswer": "The Kessel Run", "cleverWrong": "The Hydian Way" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What is the four-letter name for the species of traders that capture R2-D2 and C-3PO before selling them to Luke Skywalker?", "correctAnswer": "Jawa", "cleverWrong": "Ugnaught" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Y-wing fighters are equipped with what kind of cannons that sound positively charged?", "correctAnswer": "Ion cannons", "cleverWrong": "Laser cannons" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "The only non-Jedi to wield a lightsaber in the original \"Star Wars\" trilogy was Han Solo, when he cut open what thing?", "correctAnswer": "TaunTaun", "cleverWrong": "A Probe Droid" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "In the final episode of the first season of \"The Mandalorian,\" what famous weapon is briefly seen in the hands of Moff Gideon?", "correctAnswer": "The Darksaber", "cleverWrong": "A beskar spear" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "In the Star Wars universe, most residents of the planet Shili, including Jedi Master Shaak Ti and Padawan Ahsoka Tano, are members of what sentient humanoid species?", "correctAnswer": "Togruta", "cleverWrong": "Twi'lek" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is the name of the horned, clawed white-furred species of snow monster found on the icy planet Hoth?", "correctAnswer": "Wampas", "cleverWrong": "TaunTauns" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What is the name of the character played by Laura Dern in \"The Last Jedi\" whose namesake \"manuver\" is a kamikaze attack at lightspeed?", "correctAnswer": "Amilyn Holdo", "cleverWrong": "Captain Phasma" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "To make the TIE Fighter sound extra terrifying, legendary sound designer Ben Burtt combined the sound of cars on wet pavement with the sound of what formidable animal?", "correctAnswer": "Elephant", "cleverWrong": "Lion" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "A kerfuffle over the Darksaber and control of Mandalore sparked what Imperial genocide with a name similar to a horror franchise?", "correctAnswer": "The Great Purge", "cleverWrong": "The Night of a Thousand Tears" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Aurebesh is the writing system used to represent what spoken-word language that is the most commonly referenced in the 'Star Wars' films?", "correctAnswer": "Galactic Basic", "cleverWrong": "Huttese" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "In Star Wars, R2D2 claimed he was the property of Obi-Wan Kenobi but C3PO disagreed. Who did C3PO claim was their former master?", "correctAnswer": "Captain Antilles", "cleverWrong": "Bail Organa" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Neophyte Jedi Luke whines to Obi-Wan in \"A New Hope\" that what blocking structure keeps him from seeing during his Millennium Falcon lightsaber practice?", "correctAnswer": "Blast Shield", "cleverWrong": "Training Remote" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is the name of the large omnivorous cephalopods from the planet Vodran, having seven suckered tentacles and an eyestalk?", "correctAnswer": "Dianoga", "cleverWrong": "Sarlacc" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What much-reviled \"Star Wars\" character is a Twi'lek who served for decades as majordomo and chief of staff to Jabba the Hutt?", "correctAnswer": "Bib Fortuna", "cleverWrong": "Salacious B. Crumb" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What is Mando's real name from The Mandalorian?", "correctAnswer": "Din Djarin", "cleverWrong": "Paz Vizsla" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who was Anakin Skywalker's Padawan?", "correctAnswer": "Ahsoka Tano", "cleverWrong": "Barriss Offee" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is the name of Han Solo's ship?", "correctAnswer": "The Millennium Falcon", "cleverWrong": "The Ebon Hawk" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who acted as Queen Amidala's decoy?", "correctAnswer": "Her handmaiden Sabe", "cleverWrong": "Her sister Sola" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Finish this quote from The Mandalorian: 'This is the ___'", "correctAnswer": "Way", "cleverWrong": "Mand'alor" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Padme was Queen of what?", "correctAnswer": "Naboo", "cleverWrong": "Alderaan" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who told Anakin there is another Skywalker?", "correctAnswer": "Yoda", "cleverWrong": "Obi-Wan Kenobi" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who did Leia make acting general?", "correctAnswer": "Poe Dameron", "cleverWrong": "Finn" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Bo-Katan wanted what from Moff Gideon in The Mandalorian?", "correctAnswer": "The Darksaber", "cleverWrong": "The location of Mandalore" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Where was Baby Yoda when Order 66 was initiated?", "correctAnswer": "Coruscant", "cleverWrong": "Dagobah" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "True or False, Boba Fett survived the Sarlacc pit", "correctAnswer": "True", "cleverWrong": "False" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many episodes are in the Skywalker Saga?", "correctAnswer": "Nine", "cleverWrong": "Six" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who is known for saying the line: 'I have spoken'?", "correctAnswer": "Kuiil", "cleverWrong": "The Armorer" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who does Baby Yoda leave with in The Mandalorian Season 2 finale?", "correctAnswer": "Luke Skywalker and R2-D2", "cleverWrong": "Ahsoka Tano" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who does Obi-Wan say was the 'Chosen One'?", "correctAnswer": "Anakin", "cleverWrong": "Luke" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many children does Darth Vader have?", "correctAnswer": "Two", "cleverWrong": "One" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who said, 'I know what I have to do, but I don't know that I have the strength to do it'?", "correctAnswer": "Kylo Ren", "cleverWrong": "Anakin Skywalker" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "According to Luke, confronting what is the destiny of a Jedi?", "correctAnswer": "Fear", "cleverWrong": "The Sith" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who does Finn kiss in The Last Jedi?", "correctAnswer": "Rose", "cleverWrong": "Rey" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "What episode is Attack of the Clones?", "correctAnswer": "II", "cleverWrong": "I" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "What episode is Return of the Jedi?", "correctAnswer": "VI", "cleverWrong": "V" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Leia said never underestimate a what?", "correctAnswer": "Droid", "cleverWrong": "Wookiee" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "In which movie do Rey and Kylo kiss?", "correctAnswer": "Star Wars: The Rise of Skywalker", "cleverWrong": "Star Wars: The Last Jedi" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "X-wing fighters were used by the Resistance or the First Order?", "correctAnswer": "Resistance", "cleverWrong": "First Order" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Jyn Erso said rebellions are built on what?", "correctAnswer": "Hope", "cleverWrong": "Courage" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "Palpatine gave the command to execute what Order in Revenge of the Sith?", "correctAnswer": "66", "cleverWrong": "65" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Legend describes what as the hidden world of the Sith?", "correctAnswer": "Exegol", "cleverWrong": "Moraband" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who killed Snoke?", "correctAnswer": "Kylo Ren", "cleverWrong": "Rey" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What was Mando's weapon against Moff Gideon's darksaber?", "correctAnswer": "A beskar spear", "cleverWrong": "A vibroblade" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who is the black market droidsmith Poe knows on Kijimi?", "correctAnswer": "Babu Frik", "cleverWrong": "Peli Motto" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "What's the name of the casino city that Rose and Finn visited in The Last Jedi?", "correctAnswer": "Canto Bight", "cleverWrong": "Cloud City" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who was the spy within the First Order in The Rise of Skywalker?", "correctAnswer": "General Armitage Hux", "cleverWrong": "Captain Phasma" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What compasses lead the way to Exegol?", "correctAnswer": "A Sithway finder", "cleverWrong": "A Jedi Holocron" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What was Poe Dameron's old job before becoming a pilot?", "correctAnswer": "A spice runner", "cleverWrong": "A farmer" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Cobb Vanth had whose armor in The Mandalorian?", "correctAnswer": "Boba Fett's armor", "cleverWrong": "Jango Fett's armor" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "C-3PO is mechanically incapable of speaking translations from whom?", "correctAnswer": "The Sith", "cleverWrong": "The Hutts" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "According to Zorii, what can give free passage through any blockade and landing privileges, any vessel?", "correctAnswer": "A First Order Captain's medallion", "cleverWrong": "A writ of passage" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who famously said, 'These aren't the droids you're looking for'?", "correctAnswer": "Obi-Wan", "cleverWrong": "Luke Skywalker" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Rey and Kylo are a what ___ in the Force?", "correctAnswer": "A dyad in the Force", "cleverWrong": "A bond in the Force" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who wins by making people think they are alone?", "correctAnswer": "The First Order", "cleverWrong": "The Empire" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who voiced the horned Sith with major anger issues?", "correctAnswer": "Darth Maul", "cleverWrong": "Savage Opress" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which pointy-headed Jedi somehow stayed under the meme radar?", "correctAnswer": "Ki-Adi-Mundi", "cleverWrong": "Plo Koon" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which stormtrooper does Luke cosplay as after the Falcon's capture?", "correctAnswer": "TK-421", "cleverWrong": "FN-2187" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who zapped Palpatine so hard he turned into a raisin?", "correctAnswer": "Mace Windu", "cleverWrong": "Yoda" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who did Luke levitate to god-tier status for the Ewoks?", "correctAnswer": "C3P0", "cleverWrong": "R2-D2" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many years passed between The Phantom Menace and Attack of the Clones?", "correctAnswer": "10 Years", "cleverWrong": "12 Years" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who's married to moisture farmer Owen Lars?", "correctAnswer": "Beru", "cleverWrong": "Shmi" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who kidnapped and tortured Anakin's mum (and paid the price)?", "correctAnswer": "Tusken Raiders", "cleverWrong": "The Hutts" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who takes out Count Dooku with a double-bladed moral dilemma?", "correctAnswer": "Anakin Skywalker", "cleverWrong": "Obi-Wan Kenobi" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Whose hand takes a flying lesson at the end of Empire?", "correctAnswer": "Luke Skywalker", "cleverWrong": "Anakin Skywalker" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who cut a shady deal with Vader to save Cloud City?", "correctAnswer": "Lando Calrissian", "cleverWrong": "Lobot" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who roasted Chewie with the classic 'walking carpet' insult?", "correctAnswer": "Princess Leia", "cleverWrong": "Han Solo" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who told the Trade Federation to eliminate the Jedi guests?", "correctAnswer": "Darth Sidious", "cleverWrong": "Nute Gunray" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which two-headed alien sports bros hosted the Boonta Eve Classic Pod Race?", "correctAnswer": "Fode And Beed", "cleverWrong": "Watto" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What part of the Millennium Falcon fails more than a group project partner?", "correctAnswer": "Hyperdrive", "cleverWrong": "Landing gear" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "Fall into a Sarlacc pit, and how long will you be digested for?", "correctAnswer": "1,000 years", "cleverWrong": "100 years" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Leia hides the Death Star plans inside which brave little beep-boop?", "correctAnswer": "R2D2", "cleverWrong": "C-3PO" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who led the Gungans with lots of blubbering and big decisions?", "correctAnswer": "Rugor Nass", "cleverWrong": "Captain Tarpals" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who runs the junk shop that \"owns\" Anakin and his mom?", "correctAnswer": "Watto", "cleverWrong": "Jabba the Hutt" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What sneaky space serpent grabs Luke in the Death Star trash pool?", "correctAnswer": "Dianoga", "cleverWrong": "Dragonsnake" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who hits the brakes on the trash compactor and saves the whole squad?", "correctAnswer": "R2-D2", "cleverWrong": "C-3PO" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who tells Han, 'That's no moon'--and drops the space horror reveal of the year?", "correctAnswer": "Obi-Wan Kenobi", "cleverWrong": "Luke Skywalker" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many Dewbacks were in the original 1977 theatrical cut of the first Star Wars movie?", "correctAnswer": "Two", "cleverWrong": "Four" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which species stole the plans to the second Death Star?", "correctAnswer": "Bothans", "cleverWrong": "Mon Calamari" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What kind of trooper is introduced at the beginning of Rogue One?", "correctAnswer": "Death Troopers", "cleverWrong": "Shoretroopers" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What does AT-AT stand for?", "correctAnswer": "All Terrain Armored Transport", "cleverWrong": "All Terrain Attack Transport" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "What is the largest annual podrace in the galaxy?", "correctAnswer": "The Boonta Eve Classic", "cleverWrong": "The Vinta Harvest Classic" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "What day is Wookiee Life Day?", "correctAnswer": "November 17th", "cleverWrong": "April 25th" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Which two sectors does The Empire Strikes Back take place in?", "correctAnswer": "The Sluis Sector and The Anoat Sector", "cleverWrong": "The Arkanis Sector and The Corporate Sector" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who's the only rebel pilot to survive all three movies in the original trilogy?", "correctAnswer": "Wedge Antilles", "cleverWrong": "Biggs Darklighter" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What is the name of the imperial admiral at the beginning of The Empire Strikes Back?", "correctAnswer": "Ozzeo", "cleverWrong": "Piett" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who was the last one to jump down the Death Star's garbage chute?", "correctAnswer": "Han", "cleverWrong": "Luke" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is the name of the organization that builds a blockade around Naboo?", "correctAnswer": "The Trade Federation", "cleverWrong": "The Separatist Alliance" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many arms does the alien diner owner, Dex Jettster, have?", "correctAnswer": "Four", "cleverWrong": "Six" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "When Luke asked what was in the cave on Dagobah, what was Yoda's response?", "correctAnswer": "Only what you take with you", "cleverWrong": "Your fear" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "In what 'detention block' was Princess Leia being held in, in the first Death Star?", "correctAnswer": "AA-23", "cleverWrong": "CC-22" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What does 'TIE' stand for in TIE Fighter?", "correctAnswer": "Twin Ion Engines", "cleverWrong": "Tactical Imperial Enforcer" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who is the senator that adopts Leia, and what planet is he from?", "correctAnswer": "Senator Bail Organa, from Alderaan", "cleverWrong": "Senator Mon Mothma, from Chandrila" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What are the children being trained as Jedi called?", "correctAnswer": "Younglings", "cleverWrong": "Initiates" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What bounty hunter used a bowcaster as his weapon of choice?", "correctAnswer": "Embo", "cleverWrong": "Dengar" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is the primary reason for Anakin falling to the dark side?", "correctAnswer": "He wanted to save Padme from death during childbirth", "cleverWrong": "He desired more power than the Jedi would allow" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is the Rule of Two?", "correctAnswer": "There can only be two Sith Lords at one time", "cleverWrong": "A Sith must defeat their master to take their place" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How big is the exhaust port that is the target for Rebel Alliance Starfighters in A New Hope?", "correctAnswer": "Two meters", "cleverWrong": "One meter" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What race of alien is Admiral Ackbar?", "correctAnswer": "Mon Calamari", "cleverWrong": "Quarren" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What makes Han Solo temporarily blind after he is freed from the carbonite?", "correctAnswer": "Hibernation sickness", "cleverWrong": "Retinal scarring" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How tall is Chewbacca?", "correctAnswer": "7'6\"", "cleverWrong": "8'1\"" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "On which planet does the Resistance have its base in The Force Awakens?", "correctAnswer": "D'Qar", "cleverWrong": "Yavin IV" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who is the cantina owner on Takodana who has a lightsaber in her possession?", "correctAnswer": "Maz Kanata", "cleverWrong": "Sidon Ithano" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What is the name of Luke's childhood best friend that later served beside him in the rebellion?", "correctAnswer": "Biggs Darklighter", "cleverWrong": "Wedge Antilles" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is the red substance found on the planet Crait?", "correctAnswer": "Salt", "cleverWrong": "Kyber crystal dust" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What was Anakin Skywalker's mother's name?", "correctAnswer": "Shmi Skywalker", "cleverWrong": "Beru Lars" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who was Anakin Skywalker's father?", "correctAnswer": "He didn't have one", "cleverWrong": "Cliegg Lars" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What was The Rule of Two?", "correctAnswer": "A decree that only two Sith Lords must exist at any given time- a Master and an apprentice", "cleverWrong": "A rule that a Sith must kill their master to take their place" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Darth Vader's helmet intentionally resembles the helmet of what type of warrior?", "correctAnswer": "Samurai", "cleverWrong": "Gladiator" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What does TIE (as in TIE fighter) stand for?", "correctAnswer": "Twin Ion Engine", "cleverWrong": "Tactical Imperial Enforcer" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What war does the title Star Wars refer to?", "correctAnswer": "The Galactic Civil War", "cleverWrong": "The Clone Wars" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What was the battle in which Darth Vader sacrificed himself by destroying his Sith Master in order to save his son?", "correctAnswer": "The Battle of Endor", "cleverWrong": "The Battle of Yavin" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What finally restored balance to the Force, fulfilling Jedi prophecy?", "correctAnswer": "The death of the last two Sith Lords", "cleverWrong": "Luke Skywalker defeating Vader" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What type of fighters are flown by the Empire?", "correctAnswer": "TIE Fighters", "cleverWrong": "X-Wings" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "On what planet do Han and Chewie meet Luke?", "correctAnswer": "Tatooine", "cleverWrong": "Alderaan" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "What was the first location on which the Death Star's destructive capability is tested?", "correctAnswer": "Jeddah", "cleverWrong": "Scarif" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What creature does Chewbacca roast for dinner in The Last Jedi?", "correctAnswer": "Porgs", "cleverWrong": "Vulptex" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What species of relatively small height helped freeze Han Solo in carbonite?", "correctAnswer": "Ugnaughts", "cleverWrong": "Jawas" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "In The Book of Boba Fett what is the liquid Boba Fett sleeps in?", "correctAnswer": "A Bacta Tank", "cleverWrong": "Kolto" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which pilot had the callsign RED 6 during the Battle of Yavin?", "correctAnswer": "Porkins", "cleverWrong": "Biggs Darklighter" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Han Solo upgraded the Millennium Falcon from which stock starship?", "correctAnswer": "Corellian YT-1300f", "cleverWrong": "Corellian YT-2400" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Lando Calrissian's operation on Cloud City mines what type of gas?", "correctAnswer": "Tibanna gas", "cleverWrong": "Corusca gas" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "On what planet did General Grievous die?", "correctAnswer": "Utapau", "cleverWrong": "Mygeeto" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "In Attack of the Clones, who is the leader of the Techno Union Army?", "correctAnswer": "Watt Tambor", "cleverWrong": "San Hill" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Complete this quote: a long time ago in a", "correctAnswer": "GALAXY FAR, FAR AWAY", "cleverWrong": "in a galaxy near you" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many members of Rogue One survived?", "correctAnswer": "None", "cleverWrong": "One" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Where is the Ewok village located?", "correctAnswer": "The forest moon of Endor", "cleverWrong": "The planet of Endor" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is the name of the Rebellion's one-man space craft?", "correctAnswer": "X-Wing fighter", "cleverWrong": "B-Wing starfighter" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is the name of the Empire's one-man space craft?", "correctAnswer": "TIE-Fighter", "cleverWrong": "TIE Bomber" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "The Jedi Temple was located on what planet?", "correctAnswer": "Coruscant", "cleverWrong": "Tython" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "'This is outrageous! It's unfair!' What is Anakin Skywalker upset about?", "correctAnswer": "The Jedi Council does not grant him the rank of master", "cleverWrong": "The Council asked him to spy on Chancellor Palpatine" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "In The Force Awakens, what is Han Solo's first line?", "correctAnswer": "Chewie, we're home", "cleverWrong": "I've got a bad feeling about this" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who is the composer of the many famous Star Wars themes?", "correctAnswer": "John Williams", "cleverWrong": "Danny Elfman" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who originally owned the Millennium Falcon, and how did Han win it?", "correctAnswer": "Lando Calrissian, in a game of sabacc", "cleverWrong": "Garris Shrike, in a swoop race" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What famous Star Wars sound effect involved a vacuum cleaner and a snorkel mask?", "correctAnswer": "Darth Vader's breathing", "cleverWrong": "Chewbacca's roar" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What does Luke see in the haunted tree on Dagobah?", "correctAnswer": "Darth Vader, with Luke's own face behind the mask", "cleverWrong": "His father, Anakin, as a Jedi Knight" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What would make a fine addition to General Grievous' collection?", "correctAnswer": "Obi-Wan Kenobi's lightsaber", "cleverWrong": "Anakin Skywalker's lightsaber" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who was born first - Luke or Leia?", "correctAnswer": "Luke", "cleverWrong": "They were born simultaneously" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "What is the final line of dialogue in Rogue One?", "correctAnswer": "HOPE", "cleverWrong": "MAY THE FORCE BE WITH YOU" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Princess Leia only wears her hair down once in all of the films. Which film and when?", "correctAnswer": "Return of the Jedi, in the Ewok village", "cleverWrong": "A New Hope, during the medal ceremony" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What kind of alien is Darth Maul?", "correctAnswer": "Zabrak", "cleverWrong": "Sith Pureblood" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "In The Phantom Menace, how was the enormous Pod-racing crowd created?", "correctAnswer": "With colored cotton-tips/Q-tips", "cleverWrong": "With thousands of hand-painted miniatures" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many times does Finn use Anakin/Luke/Rey's lightsaber?", "correctAnswer": "Three times", "cleverWrong": "Once" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which character, played by the same actor, was in 10 out of 11 films?", "correctAnswer": "C-3PO, by Anthony Daniels", "cleverWrong": "R2-D2, by Kenny Baker" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "According to Orson Krennic, they were 'this close' to what?", "correctAnswer": "GREATNESS", "cleverWrong": "VICTORY" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "In Return of the Jedi, how does Obi-Wan Kenobi justify telling Luke that Darth Vader 'betrayed and murdered his father'?", "correctAnswer": "It was true from a certain point of view", "cleverWrong": "He was protecting Luke from the terrible truth" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Where did A New Hope film its desert scenes?", "correctAnswer": "Tunisia", "cleverWrong": "The Sahara Desert" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What is Padme's full name?", "correctAnswer": "Padme Amidala Naberrie", "cleverWrong": "Padme Amidala Skywalker" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "What, according to Anakin Skywalker, is coarse, rough, irritating, and gets everywhere?", "correctAnswer": "Sand", "cleverWrong": "Politics" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is the name of The First Order's super weapon in The Force Awakens?", "correctAnswer": "Starkiller Base", "cleverWrong": "The Supremacy" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What does Rey want to see in the mirror cave on Ahch-To, and what does she actually see?", "correctAnswer": "She wants to see her parents, but sees only her own reflection", "cleverWrong": "She wants to see the future, but sees only the past" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "In Solo: A Star Wars Story, who is behind Crimson Dawn?", "correctAnswer": "Darth Maul", "cleverWrong": "Qi'ra" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Finish this quote: 'Mandalorian isn't a race. It's'", "correctAnswer": "a creed", "cleverWrong": "a people" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "What does Leia say to Han before unknowingly making out with her twin brother?", "correctAnswer": "Well, I guess you don't know everything about women yet", "cleverWrong": "I'd just as soon kiss a Wookiee" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "What is Sheev Palpatine's home planet?", "correctAnswer": "Naboo", "cleverWrong": "Chandrila" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is the 'Holdo maneuver'?", "correctAnswer": "A kamikaze-style lightspeed collision with an enemy ship", "cleverWrong": "An evasive tactic to escape a tractor beam" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "How did Rey fix the Millennium Falcon's hyperdrive in The Force Awakens?", "correctAnswer": "She bypassed the compressor", "cleverWrong": "She hot-wired the ignition" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "What is the only planet to appear in all three Star Wars trilogies?", "correctAnswer": "Tatooine", "cleverWrong": "Dantooine" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What are the names of Jyn Erso's parents?", "correctAnswer": "Galen and Lyra Erso", "cleverWrong": "Corin and Sidero Erso" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is the name of The Mandalorian's ship?", "correctAnswer": "The Razor Crest", "cleverWrong": "The Ghost" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "What did Luke want to do instead of cleaning the new droids?", "correctAnswer": "Go to Tosche Station to pick up some power converters", "cleverWrong": "Join the Imperial Academy" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "In Attack of the Clones, what color dress is Padme wearing at the waterfall-meadow picnic?", "correctAnswer": "Yellow", "cleverWrong": "Blue" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many Knights of Ren are there?", "correctAnswer": "Six (not including Kylo Ren)", "cleverWrong": "Nine (not including Kylo Ren)" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "After throwing away his lightsaber, what is Ben Solo's only spoken line?", "correctAnswer": "Ow", "cleverWrong": "Rey" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who is Rose's sister, and what happens to her?", "correctAnswer": "Paige Tico. She dies in a bombing run", "cleverWrong": "Vana Tico. She is a First Order spy" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "List the first three films in CHRONOLOGICAL order.", "correctAnswer": "The Phantom Menace, Attack of the Clones, Revenge of the Sith", "cleverWrong": "Revenge of the Sith, A New Hope, The Empire Strikes Back" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "List the first three films in RELEASE order.", "correctAnswer": "A New Hope, The Empire Strikes Back, Return of the Jedi", "cleverWrong": "The Phantom Menace, Attack of the Clones, Revenge of the Sith" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is the only Star Wars film where we see two characters take a shower together?", "correctAnswer": "Solo: A Star Wars story - Han and Chewbacca", "cleverWrong": "The Last Jedi - Kylo Ren and Rey" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "In The Mandalorian, which director also voices a main character?", "correctAnswer": "Taika Waititi voices IG-11", "cleverWrong": "Dave Filoni voices Trapper Wolf" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What color do Emperor Palpatine's guards wear in Return of the Jedi?", "correctAnswer": "Red", "cleverWrong": "Crimson" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Where did Han and Leia share their first kiss?", "correctAnswer": "In the Millennium Falcon, inside a space slug", "cleverWrong": "On the Death Star, before swinging across the chasm" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who are the two imperial officers choked by Vader onscreen in The Empire Strikes Back?", "correctAnswer": "Admiral Ozzel and Captain Needa", "cleverWrong": "Admiral Piett and General Veers" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Name at least two of Queen Amidala's handmaidens.", "correctAnswer": "Sabe, Corde, and Dorme (among others)", "cleverWrong": "Shmi, Beru, and Lyra" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Complete this quote: 'You were the chosen one! It was said that you would'", "correctAnswer": "destroy the Sith, not join them!", "cleverWrong": "bring peace to the galaxy!" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "What is Rey's home planet (or at least the one she grows up on)?", "correctAnswer": "Jakku", "cleverWrong": "Pasaana" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Tobias Beckett tells Han Solo about a 'big-shot gangster putting together a crew.' Who is he talking about?", "correctAnswer": "Dryden Vos", "cleverWrong": "Jabba the Hutt" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What is the name of the Ewok that rescues Leia?", "correctAnswer": "Wicket", "cleverWrong": "Teebo" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "The phrase 'Han shot first' refers to what event?", "correctAnswer": "Han Solo shooting the bounty hunter Greedo in the Mos Eisley Cantina", "cleverWrong": "Han Solo firing on Darth Vader's TIE Fighter at the Death Star" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "When Leia is disguised as a bounty hunter in Jabba's palace, what is she holding that scares everyone?", "correctAnswer": "A thermal detonator", "cleverWrong": "A vial of coaxium" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Who said 'I slaughtered them like animals' about the Tusken Raiders?", "correctAnswer": "Anakin Skywalker", "cleverWrong": "Cliegg Lars" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What is the name of Obi-Wan Kenobi's master?", "correctAnswer": "Qui-Gon Jinn", "cleverWrong": "Sifo-Dyas" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Mark Hamill voiced a character (other than Luke) in The Rise of Skywalker - who was it?", "correctAnswer": "Boolio", "cleverWrong": "The ghost of Darth Bane" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "What does Rey say to Kylo Ren after stabbing, then Force healing him?", "correctAnswer": "I did want to take your hand. Ben's hand", "cleverWrong": "This isn't how it was supposed to be" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Director Krennic says 'Oh, it's beautiful,' as the Death Star destroys what desert city?", "correctAnswer": "Jedha City", "cleverWrong": "Scarif City" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who are the two people Luke shouts to for help when dangling at the bottom of Cloud City?", "correctAnswer": "Ben (Obi-Wan) and Leia. Leia responds", "cleverWrong": "Han and Chewie. No one responds" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What conclusion does C-3PO draw from hearing shouts in the Death Star's trash compactor?", "correctAnswer": "He thinks they're all dying", "cleverWrong": "He thinks they've found the princess's cell" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who does Din Djarin show his face to in the season one finale of The Mandalorian?", "correctAnswer": "IG-11", "cleverWrong": "Cara Dune" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many actors played Darth Vader in the original Star Wars trilogy?", "correctAnswer": "Three (body, voice, and face)", "cleverWrong": "Two (body and voice)" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is the name of Luke Skywalker's X-wing in \"Star Wars\"?", "correctAnswer": "Red 5", "cleverWrong": "Red 2" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What British actor, known for his horror film roles, played the villainous Grand Moff Tarkin in \"Star Wars\"?", "correctAnswer": "Peter Cushing", "cleverWrong": "David Prowse" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which 'Sesame Street' character and 'Star Wars' character were played by the same actor?", "correctAnswer": "The Cookie Monster and Yoda", "cleverWrong": "Oscar the Grouch and Chewbacca" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which actor links the \"Star Wars,\" \"Lord of the Rings,\" and \"James Bond\" franchises together?", "correctAnswer": "Christopher Lee", "cleverWrong": "Ian McKellen" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "In the film \"Star Wars\", who killed the bounty hunter Greedo?", "correctAnswer": "Han Solo", "cleverWrong": "Bossk" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Darth Vader was a famous villain from the \"Star Wars\" movie saga. What does the word \"Vader\" mean in Dutch?", "correctAnswer": "Father", "cleverWrong": "Dark" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What colour lightsaber did Obi-Wan Kenobi use to kill Darth Maul in the film 'Star Wars: The Phantom Menace'?", "correctAnswer": "Green", "cleverWrong": "Blue" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who was the first character to speak in the film \"Star Wars\" when it was released in 1977?", "correctAnswer": "C-3PO", "cleverWrong": "Danz Borin" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What spectral term describes a Star Wars \"Menace\", a masked man \"of the Opera\", and a \"Tollbooth\" depicted by Norton Juster in a child's novel?", "correctAnswer": "Phantom", "cleverWrong": "Ghost" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which actor starred in both \"Superman\" (1978) and \"Star Wars Episode I: The Phantom Menace\" (1999)?", "correctAnswer": "Terence Stamp", "cleverWrong": "Christopher Reeve" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "In the movie \"Star Wars\" we learn to \"use the Force\" but in the \"Star Wars\" spoof \"Spaceballs\" what do we learn to use?", "correctAnswer": "The Schwartz", "cleverWrong": "The Marshmallow" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "In the \"Star Wars\" movie franchise, what color lightsaber is shared by Darth Maul, Count Dooku, and famously, Darth Vader?", "correctAnswer": "red", "cleverWrong": "black" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What title could be used to describe Zurg from \"Toy Story\", Palpatine from \"Star Wars\", and Commodus in \"Gladiator\"?", "correctAnswer": "Emperor", "cleverWrong": "Chancellor" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Actress Carrie Fisher became famous as Princess Leia in 'Star Wars' (1977), but who was her equally famous step-mother?", "correctAnswer": "Elizabeth Taylor", "cleverWrong": "Shelley Winters" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who plays C3PO in the original \"Star Wars\" film?", "correctAnswer": "Anthony Daniels", "cleverWrong": "David Prowse" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "In \"Lawrence of Arabia\", which actor, who would later play Obi Wan Kenobi in \"Star Wars\", portrayed Prince Faisal?", "correctAnswer": "Alec Guinness", "cleverWrong": "Omar Sharif" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "In the Star Wars Universe, who is the \"Emperor's Hand\"?", "correctAnswer": "Mara Jade", "cleverWrong": "Prince Xizor" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which character in \"Star Wars\" was the first non-human to appear on the cover of \"People\" magazine?", "correctAnswer": "C-3PO", "cleverWrong": "Jabba the Hutt" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who played the role of Rey in \"Star Wars Episode VIII: The Force Awakens\"?", "correctAnswer": "Daisy Ridley", "cleverWrong": "Felicity Jones" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "In \"Star Wars\", what is the bounty hunter Dengar's ship named?", "correctAnswer": "Punishing One", "cleverWrong": "Outrider" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What \"Star Wars\" actor did the voice of Joker in many Batman cartoons?", "correctAnswer": "Mark Hamill", "cleverWrong": "Chris Farley" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "In 2012, who acquired the merchandising license to the \"Star Wars\" film series?", "correctAnswer": "The Walt Disney Company", "cleverWrong": "George Lucas bought it back" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "John Wayne, the Duke, provided, in a peculiar sort of way, the voice of a \"Star Wars\" (1977) character who goes by what name?", "correctAnswer": "Garindan", "cleverWrong": "Admiral Ackbar" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What actor who played one of the main characters in the \"Star Wars\" saga also appeared in \"The Blues Brothers\"?", "correctAnswer": "Carrie Fisher", "cleverWrong": "Harrison Ford" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Which \"Star Wars\" story sees Grand Admiral Thrawn interact with Corran Horn and his father?", "correctAnswer": "Side Trip", "cleverWrong": "X-wing: Rogue Squadron" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "During the Battle of Jakku, what Super Star Destroyer crashed on the planet?", "correctAnswer": "Ravager", "cleverWrong": "Eclipse" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What species is Zam Wessell?", "correctAnswer": "Clawdite", "cleverWrong": "Quarren" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "What did Luke Skywalker ask Yoda about his vision of the future?", "correctAnswer": "Will they die?", "cleverWrong": "Will it come true?" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Which of the Finalizer's bays did Poe & Finn steal a TIE from?", "correctAnswer": "Bay 2", "cleverWrong": "Bay 2187" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Complete the following Darth Vader quote from Star Wars: A New Hope: 'This will be a day long ___'", "correctAnswer": "Remembered", "cleverWrong": "Forgotten" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What is the name of the small, brutish desert tyrant who wants BB-8 for parts?", "correctAnswer": "Teedo", "cleverWrong": "Zuvio" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What did Yoda levitate out of the water on Dagobah?", "correctAnswer": "Luke's X-wing", "cleverWrong": "A dragonsnake" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Who snapped, 'And you said it was pretty here' on the Forest Moon of Endor?", "correctAnswer": "C-3PO", "cleverWrong": "Han Solo" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Complete the following Lando quote from Star Wars: The Empire Strikes Back: 'Why you slimy, double-crossing, no-good ____.'", "correctAnswer": "Swindler", "cleverWrong": "Scoundrel" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What item of Finn's does Captain Phasma ask to inspect at the Starkiller Base?", "correctAnswer": "His blaster", "cleverWrong": "His helmet" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What bounty hunter accosted Han Solo is the Mos Eisley cantina?", "correctAnswer": "Greedo", "cleverWrong": "IG-88" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which character pilots a TIE silencer in Star Wars: The Last Jedi?", "correctAnswer": "Kylo Ren", "cleverWrong": "Captain Phasma" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Where did Darth Vader report that the rebel fleet was massing in Star Wars: Return of the Jedi?", "correctAnswer": "Near Sullust", "cleverWrong": "Near Naboo" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many times does Finn claim Chewbacca almost killed him while he tended to his shoulder wound?", "correctAnswer": "6", "cleverWrong": "3" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is a baby porg called?", "correctAnswer": "Porglet", "cleverWrong": "Porgling" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is the first word in the opening crawl of Star Wars: The Phantom Menace?", "correctAnswer": "Turmoil", "cleverWrong": "War" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "How did Luke Skywalker address Jabba the Hutt in his holo-message?", "correctAnswer": "Exalted one", "cleverWrong": "Honorable one" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Which planet is surrounded by a dramatic ring of rocks, as seen from space?", "correctAnswer": "D'Qar", "cleverWrong": "Takodana" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Whose impression of Princess Leia aboard the Death Star was 'charming to the last'?", "correctAnswer": "Grand Moff Tarkin", "cleverWrong": "Admiral Piett" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many sand skiffs accompanied Jabba the Hutt's sail barge in Star Wars: Return of the Jedi?", "correctAnswer": "2", "cleverWrong": "3" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "What did Yoda tell Obi-Wan Kenobi he felt in Luke Skywalker?", "correctAnswer": "Much anger", "cleverWrong": "Much fear" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who is the leader of the Kanjiklub?", "correctAnswer": "Tasu Leech", "cleverWrong": "Snap Wexley" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who learned from Han Solo that the consequence of upsetting a Wookiee was getting your arms pulled out of their sockets?", "correctAnswer": "C-3PO", "cleverWrong": "Greedo" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who allowed the Rebellion to know the location of the shield generator?", "correctAnswer": "The Emperor", "cleverWrong": "Mon Mothma" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What was wrong with R5-D4?", "correctAnswer": "Bad motivator", "cleverWrong": "Bad servomotor" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Who said, 'Don't try to frighten us with your sorcerer's ways, Lord Vader'?", "correctAnswer": "Admiral Motti", "cleverWrong": "General Tagge" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who did Jabba the Hutt order into the sarlacc pit first?", "correctAnswer": "Luke Skywalker", "cleverWrong": "Chewbacca" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What do First Order stormtrooper helmets not filter out, according to Finn?", "correctAnswer": "Toxins", "cleverWrong": "Smoke" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who arrived just before Han Solo at Cloud City, leaving Lando Calrissian no choice but to betray his old friend?", "correctAnswer": "Darth Vader", "cleverWrong": "Jabba the Hutt" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who impersonated an AT-ST pilot, getting the Imperials to open the bunker door?", "correctAnswer": "Han Solo", "cleverWrong": "Chewbacca" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Complete the following Leia quote from Star Wars: The Empire Strikes Back: 'Why, you stuck up- half-witted- ___ ...Nerf-herder!'", "correctAnswer": "Scruffy-looking", "cleverWrong": "Foul-smelling" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What kind of ship does General Hux call the Millennium Falcon?", "correctAnswer": "Corellian YT model freighter", "cleverWrong": "Baleen-class bulk freighter" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Who exclaimed, 'HE's the brains, sweetheart'?", "correctAnswer": "Han Solo", "cleverWrong": "Chewbacca" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who did Luke Skywalker say was on the ship requesting the shuttle Tydirium's code clearance?", "correctAnswer": "Darth Vader", "cleverWrong": "Admiral Piett" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What did C-3PO 'thank the maker' for in Star Wars: A New Hope?", "correctAnswer": "An oil bath", "cleverWrong": "A restart" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who was 2-1B's assistant in Echo Base?", "correctAnswer": "FX-7", "cleverWrong": "FX-12" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "When do First Order stormtroopers start their exceptional training and programming?", "correctAnswer": "At birth", "cleverWrong": "Age 3" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which of the following words did Poe Dameron use to describe General Hux during his radio communique?", "correctAnswer": "Pasty", "cleverWrong": "Lackey" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What did the Ewoks use in their initial attack on the Imperial forces outside the rear entrance to the shield generator bunker?", "correctAnswer": "Bows and arrows", "cleverWrong": "Catapults" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who introduced Obi-Wan Kenobi and Luke Skywalker to Han Solo?", "correctAnswer": "Chewbacca", "cleverWrong": "BoShek" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "To what was C-3PO referring when he screamed, 'Oh, go away! Beastly thing! Shoo! Shoo!'?", "correctAnswer": "A mynock", "cleverWrong": "A wampa" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Complete the following Obi-Wan Kenobi quote from Star Wars: A New Hope: 'Your ___ can deceive you, don't trust them.'", "correctAnswer": "Eyes", "cleverWrong": "Thoughts" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What word does Supreme Leader Snoke use to refer to Rey when he finds out she was able to resist Kylo's powers?", "correctAnswer": "Scavenger", "cleverWrong": "Girl" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What did Darth Vader tell Luke Skywalker that Obi-Wan had been wise to hide from Vader?", "correctAnswer": "Princess Leia", "cleverWrong": "Master Yoda" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "According to C-3PO, in how many locations was the tractor beam coupled to the main reactor on the Death Star?", "correctAnswer": "7", "cleverWrong": "9" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Which device acts as a rehabilitation chamber for Luke after he was attacked by a wampa on Hoth?", "correctAnswer": "Bacta tank", "cleverWrong": "Carbon-freezing chamber" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who volunteered to lead the attack against the second Death Star?", "correctAnswer": "Lando Calrissian", "cleverWrong": "Chewbacca" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many banthas did Luke Skywalker spot after R2-D2 had alerted him that several creatures were approaching from the southeast?", "correctAnswer": "2", "cleverWrong": "3" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who ordered Han Solo to be placed in the carbon freeze to test it on a living being before using it on Luke Skywalker?", "correctAnswer": "Darth Vader", "cleverWrong": "Boba Fett" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What color are the eyes of the creature that watches BB-8 roll away from the destroyed village on Jakku?", "correctAnswer": "Red", "cleverWrong": "Blue" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "According to Luke Skywalker, whose weakness was their overconfidence?", "correctAnswer": "The Emperor", "cleverWrong": "Han Solo" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Who said, 'You're all clear, kid! Now let's blow this thing and go home'?", "correctAnswer": "Han Solo", "cleverWrong": "Biggs Darklighter" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which Imperial officer was in charge of the ground assault against the Rebels on Hoth?", "correctAnswer": "General Veers", "cleverWrong": "Admiral Ozzel" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "How long did Luke Skywalker tell the stormtrooper patrol in Mos Eisley he had owned R2-D2 and C-3PO?", "correctAnswer": "3-4 seasons", "cleverWrong": "2-3 seasons" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What kind of Imperial ship's hull do Rey and Finn fly through while escaping Jakku in the Millennium Falcon?", "correctAnswer": "Super Star Destroyer", "cleverWrong": "Bulk freighter" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What was Han Solo's rank in the Rebel Alliance at the Battle of Hoth?", "correctAnswer": "Captain", "cleverWrong": "General" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Who said, 'You have paid the price for your lack of vision'?", "correctAnswer": "Emperor Palpatine", "cleverWrong": "Grand Moff Tarkin" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who informed Princess Leia that the shield doors to the Echo Base on Hoth had to be closed for the night?", "correctAnswer": "Bren Derlin", "cleverWrong": "General Rieekan" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who frees a desperate BB-8 from a net while he's being dragged behind the luggabeast?", "correctAnswer": "Rey", "cleverWrong": "Teedo" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How fast past lightspeed did Han Solo say the Millennium Falcon could go?", "correctAnswer": "0.5", "cleverWrong": "0.6" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What guild did Princess Leia ask Lando whether Cloud City was a part of?", "correctAnswer": "Mining Guild", "cleverWrong": "Tibanna Guild" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Whom did R2-D2 push overboard on Jabba the Hutt's sail barge?", "correctAnswer": "C-3PO", "cleverWrong": "Salacious B. Crumb" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "To whom did Darth Vader make a point of stressing, 'No disintegrations'?", "correctAnswer": "Boba Fett", "cleverWrong": "IG-88" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What are the colors of the two squads of X-wings that fly with Poe Dameron to Starkiller Base?", "correctAnswer": "Blue and red", "cleverWrong": "Blue and green" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What did Han Solo ask Chewbacca to bring him when he was trying to repair the hyperdrive motivator?", "correctAnswer": "A hydrospanner", "cleverWrong": "A coupling" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What was Grand Moff Tarkin's first name?", "correctAnswer": "Wilhuff", "cleverWrong": "Maurice" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What was Figrin D'an's species?", "correctAnswer": "Bith", "cleverWrong": "Rodian" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What does Omega and Wrecker end every successful mission with?", "correctAnswer": "Mantell Mix", "cleverWrong": "A meiloorun fruit" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Where did C-3PO tell stormtroopers who entered the control room on the Death Star he had to take his counterpart?", "correctAnswer": "To maintenance", "cleverWrong": "To the repair shop" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What do the 'people who knew him best' think Luke Skywalker went looking for after he disappeared?", "correctAnswer": "The first Jedi Temple", "cleverWrong": "Justice" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Complete the following Princess Leia quote from A New Hope: '____ short for a stormtrooper?'", "correctAnswer": "Aren't you a little", "cleverWrong": "You're a bit" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "What docking bay in Mos Eisley housed the Millennium Falcon?", "correctAnswer": "Docking bay 94", "cleverWrong": "Docking bay 77" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Where were the Yavin 4 scenes in Star Wars: A New Hope shot?", "correctAnswer": "Guatemala", "cleverWrong": "Venezuela" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What self-imposed state has R2-D2 been in 'ever since Master Luke went away'?", "correctAnswer": "Low power mode", "cleverWrong": "Sleep mode" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who directed Star Wars: Return of the Jedi?", "correctAnswer": "Richard Marquand", "cleverWrong": "Lawrence Kasdan" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What does BB-8 use on the Millennium Falcon to stay upright during the turbulent flight leaving Jakku?", "correctAnswer": "Cable launchers", "cleverWrong": "Webbing" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What, according to R2-D2, were the chances of surviving the harsh night weather of Hoth?", "correctAnswer": "725 to 1", "cleverWrong": "893 to 1" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What does Poe Dameron tell Finn he can keep because it suits him?", "correctAnswer": "His jacket", "cleverWrong": "His blaster" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Complete the C-3PO quote from A New Hope: ' I am C-3PO, human-cyborg relations. And this is my ____ R2-D2'", "correctAnswer": "Counterpart", "cleverWrong": "Best friend" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "What is the name of the outpost that is closest to where Rey lives on Jakku?", "correctAnswer": "Niima", "cleverWrong": "Mos Eisley" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Where did Princess Leia send all troops in sector twelve during the Imperial invasion of Echo Base?", "correctAnswer": "South slope", "cleverWrong": "North slope" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What Super Star Destroyer was Darth Vader's flagship?", "correctAnswer": "Executor", "cleverWrong": "Eclipse" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What type of ship did General Solo use to infiltrate the shield surrounding the forest moon of Endor?", "correctAnswer": "Lambda-class shuttle", "cleverWrong": "TIE bomber" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What kind of wrench does Rey ask Finn to retrieve when she's making repairs on the Millennium Falcon?", "correctAnswer": "Harris", "cleverWrong": "Hydro" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What did hibernation sickness do to Han Solo?", "correctAnswer": "He couldn't see", "cleverWrong": "He couldn't breathe" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Who said, 'I recognized your foul stench when I was brought on board'?", "correctAnswer": "Princess Leia", "cleverWrong": "Luke Skywalker" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What were the rebels targeting in their attack on the Death Star?", "correctAnswer": "Thermal exhaust port", "cleverWrong": "Antigravity chamber" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who rescued Luke Skywalker from the Tusken Raiders?", "correctAnswer": "Obi-Wan Kenobi", "cleverWrong": "Biggs Darklighter" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What does Rey call Finn when she first meets him?", "correctAnswer": "A thief", "cleverWrong": "A member of the Resistance" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What was Luke Skywalker's rank in the Rebel Alliance at the Battle of Hoth?", "correctAnswer": "Commander", "cleverWrong": "Lieutenant" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many lessons does Luke Skywalker offer to give to Rey?", "correctAnswer": "3", "cleverWrong": "1" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What did the rancor in Jabba's Palace eat right before turning his attention to Luke Skywalker?", "correctAnswer": "A Gamorrean", "cleverWrong": "A Kowakian Monkey-Lizard" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Ezra Bridger first met the Ghost crew while they are stealing what from the Imperials?", "correctAnswer": "Blasters", "cleverWrong": "Meilooruns" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which former enemy must Obi-Wan unite with in order to defend himself against Savage Opress and Darth Maul?", "correctAnswer": "Asajj Ventress", "cleverWrong": "Cad Bane" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who is the captain of Dryden Vos's security forces?", "correctAnswer": "Aemon Gremm", "cleverWrong": "Aurodia Ventafoli" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "The creature a thirsty Finn joins for a drink of water on Jakku is called what?", "correctAnswer": "Happabore", "cleverWrong": "Luggabeast" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many TIE fighters does Finn take out when escaping Jakku on the Falcon?", "correctAnswer": "2", "cleverWrong": "3" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Who said, 'Twilight is upon me, and soon night must fall'?", "correctAnswer": "Yoda", "cleverWrong": "Darth Vader" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who places the secret plans into R2-D2's memory banks?", "correctAnswer": "Princess Leia", "cleverWrong": "Jan Dodonna" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many Star Destroyers did Han Solo see coming right at the Millennium Falcon after it blasted out of Echo Base?", "correctAnswer": "2", "cleverWrong": "3" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What well known director voices Pre Vizsla, the leader of the Death Watch?", "correctAnswer": "Jon Favreau", "cleverWrong": "Dave Filoni" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What did Luke Skywalker give Jabba the Hutt as a token of his goodwill?", "correctAnswer": "R2-D2 and C-3PO", "cleverWrong": "50,000 credits" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many ships remained in the Resistance fleet after the attack over D-Qar?", "correctAnswer": "4", "cleverWrong": "5" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What creature did Luke Skywalker bullseye in Beggar's Canyon?", "correctAnswer": "Womp rats", "cleverWrong": "Banthas" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "According to Captain Phasma, FN-2187 was evaluated and sent for what?", "correctAnswer": "Reconditioning", "cleverWrong": "Termination" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What is the name of Wrecker's tooka doll?", "correctAnswer": "Lula", "cleverWrong": "Wrecker Jr" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "When Darth Vader said, 'He will join us or die.' to whom was he referring?", "correctAnswer": "Luke Skywalker", "cleverWrong": "Han Solo" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who rescues Finn and Rose on Canto Bight?", "correctAnswer": "DJ and BB-8", "cleverWrong": "Chewbacca and BB-8" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Which device is used by Luke Skywalker aboard the Millennium Falcon to test his early lightsaber skills?", "correctAnswer": "Training remote", "cleverWrong": "Probe droid" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many rathtars did Han Solo have in his freighter's cargo holds?", "correctAnswer": "3", "cleverWrong": "4" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many quad laser cannons does the Millennium Falcon have?", "correctAnswer": "2", "cleverWrong": "1" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who gets Poe Dameron to reveal the location of the map leading to Luke Skywalker?", "correctAnswer": "Kylo Ren", "cleverWrong": "Captain Phasma" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Complete the following Luke Skywalker quote. 'Impressive. Every word in that sentence was ___.'", "correctAnswer": "Wrong", "cleverWrong": "Nonsense" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "For which planet did Grand Moff Tarkin tell Admiral Motti to set the Death Star's course?", "correctAnswer": "Alderaan", "cleverWrong": "Dantooine" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What job did Han Solo offer Rey when they arrived on Takodana?", "correctAnswer": "Second Mate", "cleverWrong": "Co-Pilot" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What did Leia order the Resistance fleet to do as it fled from the First Order in The Last Jedi?", "correctAnswer": "Get out of range", "cleverWrong": "Attack their ships" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who greeted Luke Skywalker at the entrance of Jabba's Palace in Return of the Jedi?", "correctAnswer": "Bib Fortuna", "cleverWrong": "Oola" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Which type of vessel did Luke Skywalker use to escape the second Death Star?", "correctAnswer": "Lambda-class shuttle", "cleverWrong": "TIE interceptor" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is Hoth covered in?", "correctAnswer": "Snow and ice", "cleverWrong": "Grassy plains" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What did Princess Leia have that scared Wicket?", "correctAnswer": "A helmet", "cleverWrong": "A snack" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What type of weapons does General Hux order to be used to stop the fleeing TIE fighter containing Poe and Finn?", "correctAnswer": "Ventral cannons", "cleverWrong": "Ion Cannons" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What are the large creatures that race on Canto Bight?", "correctAnswer": "Fathiers", "cleverWrong": "Thala-sirens" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Complete the following Obi-Wan Kenobi quote: '___ It's a space station.'", "correctAnswer": "That's no moon", "cleverWrong": "That's not a moon" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What's the name of the Bad Batch's ship?", "correctAnswer": "Marauder", "cleverWrong": "Solstice" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "The Millennium Falcon hides from the Empire in a cave that turns out to be which creature?", "correctAnswer": "Space Slug", "cleverWrong": "Sarlacc" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What does Luke Skywalker call the beings who have kept up the Jedi structures since they were built on Ahch-To?", "correctAnswer": "Caretakers", "cleverWrong": "Custodians" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What was Finn's job as a stormtrooper on Starkiller Base?", "correctAnswer": "Sanitation", "cleverWrong": "Maintenance" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "What did Princess Leia tell Luke Skywalker when he saw her being escorted by stormtroopers in Cloud City?", "correctAnswer": "It's a trap!", "cleverWrong": "Watch Out!" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which of these clones isn't a member of the Bad Batch?", "correctAnswer": "Hunter", "cleverWrong": "Cutup" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What does Wrecker have a fear of in the episode 'On the Wings of Keeradaks'?", "correctAnswer": "Heights", "cleverWrong": "Keeradaks" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "All the Bad Batch members are considered 'clone commandos' aside from Echo who is...", "correctAnswer": "An Advanced Recon Commando", "cleverWrong": "A Clone Sergeant" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What's the official Republic designation for the clone also known as Echo?", "correctAnswer": "CT-1409", "cleverWrong": "CT-4040" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Where was the Bad Batch fighting before Commander Cody requested their help on Anaxes?", "correctAnswer": "Pantora", "cleverWrong": "Yalbec Prime" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who was Rogue Leader in the Battle of Hoth?", "correctAnswer": "Luke Skywalker", "cleverWrong": "Wes Janson" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What does Rey not see in the Force on Ahch-To?", "correctAnswer": "Luke Skywalker", "cleverWrong": "Violence" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "According to Lor San Tekka, there can be no balance to the Force without what?", "correctAnswer": "The Jedi", "cleverWrong": "The map to Luke Skywalker" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who was the first to volunteer for Han Solo's command crew on their mission to Endor?", "correctAnswer": "Chewbacca", "cleverWrong": "Leia Organa" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who did Darth Vader know was on the Death Star by feeling a tremor in the Force?", "correctAnswer": "Obi-Wan Kenobi", "cleverWrong": "The Millennium Falcon" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "What does Rose call Finn when they first meet?", "correctAnswer": "THE Finn", "cleverWrong": "A legend" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Who exclaimed, 'Into the garbage chute, fly boy!'?", "correctAnswer": "Princess Leia", "cleverWrong": "Luke Skywalker" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who commandeered an AT-ST during the Battle of Endor?", "correctAnswer": "Chewbacca", "cleverWrong": "C-3PO" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "At the Resistance base on D'Qar, Han tells Leia there was too much ____ in their son?", "correctAnswer": "Vader", "cleverWrong": "Darkness" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who made an announcement to the facility on Cloud City to leave before more troops arrived?", "correctAnswer": "Lando Calrissian", "cleverWrong": "Princess Leia" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who was Lando Calrissian's copilot aboard the Millennium Falcon during the Battle of Endor?", "correctAnswer": "Nien Nunb", "cleverWrong": "Admiral Ackbar" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What accessory does Maz Kanata say the master codebreaker will be wearing?", "correctAnswer": "A Red Plom Bloom", "cleverWrong": "A Corellian Pendant" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "To whom did Red Leader exclaim, 'Cut the chatter' during the Battle of Yavin?", "correctAnswer": "Red Two", "cleverWrong": "Red Three" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What do the Resistance fighters plan to target in their attack on Starkiller Base?", "correctAnswer": "Thermal Oscillator", "cleverWrong": "The Planet Core" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Darth Vader told Luke Skywalker there was only one thing Luke could use to destroy him. What was it?", "correctAnswer": "Luke's Anger", "cleverWrong": "The Force" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Which ridge did Owen Lars want R2-D2 and C-3PO to be working on in the morning?", "correctAnswer": "South", "cleverWrong": "North" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who told Luke that there was another Skywalker?", "correctAnswer": "Yoda", "cleverWrong": "The Emperor" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Which ship was Rey's first pick to escape from the attacking TIE fighters on Jakku?", "correctAnswer": "A Quad-jumper", "cleverWrong": "A landspeeder" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "According to Obi-Wan Kenobi, what was not to be travelled lightly?", "correctAnswer": "The Jundland Wastes", "cleverWrong": "Beggar's Canyon" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "During the battle over D-Qar, BB-8 is called upon to repair which component of Poe's X-wing?", "correctAnswer": "Weapons Systems", "cleverWrong": "Hyperdrive" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "In what detention block of section AA was Princess Leia being held on the Death Star?", "correctAnswer": "23", "cleverWrong": "24" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What sound draws Rey into Maz's castle basement?", "correctAnswer": "A young girl crying", "cleverWrong": "Hum of a lightsaber" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "How does General Organa greet Poe Dameron when he returns from his mission against the dreadnought?", "correctAnswer": "Slaps him", "cleverWrong": "Embraces him" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What, according to Yoda, was 'quicker, easier, more seductive'?", "correctAnswer": "The dark side", "cleverWrong": "The light side" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many pilots can an AT-ST accommodate?", "correctAnswer": "2", "cleverWrong": "4" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What dish does Yoda cook for Luke on Dagobah?", "correctAnswer": "Rootleaf Stew", "cleverWrong": "Colo Claw Fish" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "How did Han Solo tell Chewbacca to fly as they were approaching the second Death Star?", "correctAnswer": "Casual", "cleverWrong": "Cool" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What structure did Rey use as a dwelling on Jakku?", "correctAnswer": "A Downed AT-AT", "cleverWrong": "A Scrap Heap" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "What is the first question Luke asks Rey on Ahch-To?", "correctAnswer": "How did you find me?", "cleverWrong": "Who are you?" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many Resistance deserters did Rose stun before meeting Finn?", "correctAnswer": "3", "cleverWrong": "7" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What household item was used as miniature background spectators in the podrace shots in The Phantom Menace?", "correctAnswer": "Q-Tips", "cleverWrong": "Clothespins" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Whose face did Luke Skywalker see in Darth Vader's helmet after defeating a vision of him in the cave on Dagobah?", "correctAnswer": "Luke Skywalker", "cleverWrong": "Anakin Skywalker" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "What price did Jabba settle on for Chewbacca from the bounty hunter Boussh?", "correctAnswer": "35,000", "cleverWrong": "50,000" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who was the 'moof milker' who put a compressor on the Millennium Falcon's ignition line?", "correctAnswer": "Unkar Plutt", "cleverWrong": "Teedo" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Complete the following Darth Vader quote: 'When I left you, I was but the learner, now I am the ___'", "correctAnswer": "Master", "cleverWrong": "Teacher" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What did Admiral Piett call the bounty hunters assembled on the bridge of the Executor?", "correctAnswer": "Scum", "cleverWrong": "Trash" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many clawed fingers does a rancor have on each deadly hand?", "correctAnswer": "Four", "cleverWrong": "Three" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What does BB-8 blast at the Canto Bight Police officers?", "correctAnswer": "Coins", "cleverWrong": "Electricity" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What color is Obi-Wan Kenobi's lightsaber?", "correctAnswer": "Blue", "cleverWrong": "Purple" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "What is the galactic placement of the planet Geonosis?", "correctAnswer": "Outer Rim", "cleverWrong": "Mid Rim" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How old was Warwick Davis when he played Wicket in Return of the Jedi?", "correctAnswer": "11", "cleverWrong": "14" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What did the crew of The Last Jedi nickname BB-9E on set?", "correctAnswer": "BB-Hate", "cleverWrong": "BB-9" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Which young bounty hunter plotted to assassinate Mace Windu during the Duel on Coruscant?", "correctAnswer": "Boba Fett", "cleverWrong": "Aurra Sing" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How old was Padme Amidala when she joined the Legislative Youth Program?", "correctAnswer": "12", "cleverWrong": "11" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Who exclaimed, 'Around the survivors, a perimeter create!' during the Battle of Geonosis?", "correctAnswer": "Yoda", "cleverWrong": "Kit Fisto" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many moons does Tatooine have?", "correctAnswer": "3", "cleverWrong": "2" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "In A New Hope, what did C-3PO enjoy after a long hard day on Tatooine?", "correctAnswer": "An oil bath", "cleverWrong": "A nap" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What was R2-D2 tasked with doing on Jabba the Hutt's sail barge in Return of the Jedi?", "correctAnswer": "Serving Drinks", "cleverWrong": "Playing Music" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many portions does Unkar Plutt offer Rey for BB-8 in The Force Awakens?", "correctAnswer": "60", "cleverWrong": "50" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "Who set off a trap, allowing the rebels to be captured by the Ewoks in Return of the Jedi?", "correctAnswer": "Chewbacca", "cleverWrong": "R2-D2" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What is a group of porgs called?", "correctAnswer": "A murder", "cleverWrong": "A flock" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "In Star Wars Rebels, what does Sabine give to Ezra as a birthday present?", "correctAnswer": "A picture of his family", "cleverWrong": "A holocron" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "What is the name of the Rebellion hideout on the ice planet Hoth?", "correctAnswer": "Echo Base", "cleverWrong": "Delta Base" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "When Kylo Ren interrogates Rey after her capture on Takodana, what does he ask her to tell him?", "correctAnswer": "About the droid", "cleverWrong": "Who she is" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "What battle started the Clone Wars?", "correctAnswer": "Battle of Geonosis", "cleverWrong": "Battle of Coruscant" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many TIE fighters escorted Darth Vader's shuttle as it approached the second Death Star?", "correctAnswer": "Two", "cleverWrong": "Four" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "In The Force Awakens, what kind of helmet does Rey put on while she eats her meal?", "correctAnswer": "X-wing pilot", "cleverWrong": "TIE fighter pilot" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "quotes", "question": "Who said, 'if he gets a translator, be sure it speaks Bocce'?", "correctAnswer": "Beru Lars", "cleverWrong": "Owen Lars" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "What color is Kit Fisto's lightsaber?", "correctAnswer": "Green", "cleverWrong": "Blue" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Which of these planets did NOT appear in Solo: A Star Wars Story?", "correctAnswer": "Kashyyyk", "cleverWrong": "Kessel" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "other", "question": "Which nickname is NOT used for Chopper by the Ghost crew?", "correctAnswer": "Bucket of Junk", "cleverWrong": "Metal Menace" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How tall was Jar Jar Binks?", "correctAnswer": "1.96 meters", "cleverWrong": "2.20 meters" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "numbers", "question": "How many arms do Besalisks, like Dexter Jettster, have?", "correctAnswer": "Four", "cleverWrong": "Six" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "What is the name of Asajj Ventress' homeworld?", "correctAnswer": "Dathomir", "cleverWrong": "Dantooine" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "names", "question": "On a shopping trip on Coruscant, who was abducted by the bounty hunter Cad Bane?", "correctAnswer": "C-3PO & R2-D2", "cleverWrong": "Aurra Sing" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Which planet is the homeworld of the Mon Calamari?", "correctAnswer": "Mon Cala", "cleverWrong": "Kamino" },
    { "type": "trivia", "category": "places", "question": "Luke Skywalker's island on Ahch-To was filmed on which real-world island located in Ireland?", "correctAnswer": "Skellig Michael", "cleverWrong": "Isle of Skye" }
  ]
}